{"question": "Place a point I. Mark point Y at a distance of 2.4 from point I in an arbitrary direction. Find point S such that point Y is the midpoint of the segment from I to S. Form segment U joining points S and Y. Find the length of segment SY.", "answer": "2.4", "hash": "8bacf8f40ff8bb20bcbe494d33a54acdbaae052ea32a6d3ac11b72fd4f02168e", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_481.txt"}
{"question": "Create a point D. Construct a point U at distance D from point 4. Find point V such that point U is the midpoint of the segment from D to V. Construct a line C through points U and V. Create point J on line C so that its distance from point U is 1.7. Create a regular 4-sided polygon beginning at points D and J, name the additional vertices ['A', 'N'], and denote the polygon as L. Compute O1 as the length of segment segment JA raised to the power of 1. Calculate the value of O1.", "answer": "5.7", "hash": "80db80de7e081fa37f11180284eb310e0fa5d83a46f5aa1efab07ba274de0836", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_619.txt"}
{"question": "Create a point D. Position point E at a distance of 2.0 from point D, in whichever direction you choose. Construct segment W from point E to point D. What is the length of segment ED?", "answer": "2.0", "hash": "f8616e7fe9844b96a41eb60a514864988534d2cd82eaedf02d5f5abb9d8b2096", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_284.txt"}
{"question": "Mark a point W. Place point J so that it is 2.4 units away from point W in any direction. Construct a circle N with center J passing through point W. Determine the radius G of circle N. Compute the value of G.", "answer": "2.4", "hash": "e65e4c9e96e3d320f7c565a9d768651234643a7c2c61e4dc23db55385260561e", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_811.txt"}
{"question": "Place a point U. Create a point H. Place point W so that it is 2.9 units away from point U in any direction. Create a point Y at a distance of H from point 10. Construct the perpendicular bisector T of points H and U. Find the length B between points W and Y. Find line O by reflecting line T through point U. Create point S on line O so that its distance from point Y is 4.6. Form a circle M centered at S with a distance of B from center to circumference. Compute the value J equal to the radius of circle M. Calculate the ratio G of measure J to measure B. Compute the value of G.", "answer": "1.0", "hash": "ad99071be5371f98a0022d0a62e0f72e94421d8f13bfc681471f5c4c2e36bf45", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_786.txt"}
{"question": "Construct a point X. Position a point G so that it is exactly X units from point 6. Locate the midpoint K between points X and G. Create the line E that perpendicularly bisects the segment between points X and K. Find point Y such that point K is the midpoint of the segment from X to Y. Create line B as the reflection of line E across point Y. Mark point W on line B at a distance of 2.5 from point G. Find the length H between points W and K. Compute the value of H.", "answer": "7.9057", "hash": "42c39c3bcc03a2c3bafdec96278ec62bca4b8f57db6b7c65fff321c8b890c869", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_834.txt"}
{"question": "Create a point F. Create point M such that it lies 1.3 units from point F in any direction. Form the perpendicular bisector J of the segment from point M to point F. Find point Q such that line J is the perpendicular bisector of segment from M to Q. Place point Y so that it is 4.4 units away from point Q in any direction. Determine the distance I from point Q to point Y. Compute the value of I.", "answer": "4.4", "hash": "8429475c8e822e81451cbd0204146926afb1e52e62bc0cd7aa638bfec9bd1815", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_293.txt"}
{"question": "Place a point H. Mark a point B. Form a circle R centered at point B such that point H lies on it. Form the perpendicular bisector W of the segment from point B to point H. Determine the points P and X where circle R intersects line W. Find the measure of angle V formed by points X, H, and P. Find the measure of angle XHP.", "answer": "2.0944", "hash": "e718c50b7997005da5f2704a3054eb72e085dc08a9e7de669b42f65e7c69ee6e", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_120.txt"}
{"question": "Position a point D. Create point P such that it lies 3.6 units from point D in any direction. Construct a regular polygon with 1 sides starting from points D and P, call the new vertices ['R'], and label the resulting polygon as L. Compute E as the length of segment segment DD raised to the power of 1. Compute M5 as measure E raised to the power of 2. Calculate the value of M5.", "answer": "12.96", "hash": "25951eb6696ac05cd8d774f54b571ebc0362805461b98d84fe9b0c9f53fb3975", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_618.txt"}
{"question": "Create a point Q. Calculate the difference W between measures 2.3 and 1.4. Mark point I at a distance of 1.2 from point Q in an arbitrary direction. Construct a regular polygon with 4 sides starting from points Q and I, call the new vertices ['S', 'R'], and label the resulting polygon as C. Calculate the area O8 of polygon C. Compute J3 as the ratio of measure W to measure O8. Calculate the value of J3.", "answer": "0.625", "hash": "cc49533597860e88e200dc63fe83fb1f4a033e5aac1147a4f86454f64aa51b40", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_466.txt"}
{"question": "Create a point I. Place a point F that is I units away from point 4. Construct a regular polygon with 5 sides starting from points F and I, call the new vertices ['V', 'H', 'T'], and label the resulting polygon as Q. Draw the perpendicular bisector X that divides segment segment TF into two equal parts. Establish a circle A with center H and radius equal to the distance from H to F. Identify the point K at the middle of segment segment TF. Find the intersection points C and G of circle A and line X. Create a regular 8-sided polygon beginning at points C and K, name the additional vertices ['Y5', 'W3', 'A3', 'W6', 'N4', 'B7'], and denote the polygon as Z4. What is the area of polygon Z4?", "answer": "15.6582", "hash": "0037d7d5e9902b5d94f9c15bc08b63a1111e17319a466ff5817476a931770cec", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_969.txt"}
{"question": "Mark a point U. Mark point H at a distance of 1.7 from point U in an arbitrary direction. Construct segment C from point U to point H. Compute T as the length of segment segment UH raised to the power of 1. Compute the value of T.", "answer": "1.7", "hash": "0a045a2a5547b5056b32b282ee5fc8b13e5a021ce46d2eb3ed4e16e58eadee6c", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_929.txt"}
{"question": "Construct a point U. Construct a point O at distance U from point 4. Construct point I at distance 2.7 from point O in a random direction. Construct a regular polygon with 8 sides starting from points O and I, call the new vertices ['Q', 'A', 'S', 'G', 'M', 'Y'], and label the resulting polygon as X. Find the area Z1 enclosed by polygon X. Compute V2 as measure Z1 raised to the power of 2. Calculate the value of V2.", "answer": "1238.9861", "hash": "00d433da57d763ab697d7efe6cb09244f6dab2461f2809b78b462b722d47207e", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_18.txt"}
{"question": "Create a point F. Position a point L so that it is exactly F units from point 4. Create a regular 8-sided polygon beginning at points L and F, name the additional vertices ['A', 'Y', 'H', 'R', 'M', 'T8'], and denote the polygon as E. Compute Y1 as the length of segment segment AY raised to the power of 7. Compute the value of Y1.", "answer": "16384.0", "hash": "9c747540a18d3826ae7afb34b100bc8946f64bd3806e59269d42131f9b2b9d75", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_918.txt"}
{"question": "Create a point F. Create point H such that it lies 3.4 units from point F in any direction. Find point Q such that point F is the midpoint of the segment from H to Q. Find the midpoint P of points Q and H. Measure the distance Z between points P and H. Calculate the value of Z.", "answer": "3.4", "hash": "c4edf5ab878550d99b9f37f9bcdd76d4df4d39fae880775e374b6fe652a73782", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_850.txt"}
{"question": "Construct a point D. Construct a point E at distance D from point 4. Form a circle J centered at point E such that point D lies on it. Invert point D with respect to circle J, and call the resulting point K. Create a regular 3-sided polygon beginning at points E and K, name the additional vertices ['V'], and denote the polygon as U. Compute S6 as the length of segment segment EK raised to the power of 7. Compute the value of S6.", "answer": "16384.0", "hash": "0548f675bed7a911a87956ef39aace40003721ff9ab7bbd11c77101419cb2be4", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_633.txt"}
{"question": "Construct a point B. Construct point Q at distance 1.1 from point B in a random direction. Construct a regular polygon with 9 sides starting from points Q and B, call the new vertices ['S', 'M', 'O', 'G', 'J', 'P', 'K'], and label the resulting polygon as X. Compute the length I of the straight line from point Q to point G. Compute the value of I.", "answer": "3.1673", "hash": "3dc20e884ca4b4733601bceb9999cb3df05aefe38bd168b0e44da57df566826e", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_740.txt"}
{"question": "Place a point E. Place a point R that is E units away from point 2. Draw a line segment D connecting points R and E. Mark the point B that is equidistant from both endpoints of segment segment RE. Draw a line segment M connecting points B and R. What is the length of segment BR?", "answer": "1.0", "hash": "dc47fc4f0eac8c658857662cc5830cae2e44c9fd08aded48aeb9cc1635e9067b", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_707.txt"}
{"question": "Position a point Q. Create point W such that it lies 4.4 units from point Q in any direction. Create a regular 3-sided polygon beginning at points Q and W, name the additional vertices ['P'], and denote the polygon as A. Construct a regular polygon with 10 sides starting from points Q and P, call the new vertices ['L', 'M', 'Q9', 'D1', 'Y6', 'B5', 'M8', 'S1'], and label the resulting polygon as O. Reflect point Q9 across segment segment D1Y6, and call the resulting point O3. Establish a line segment E2 from point M8 to point O3. Find the length of segment M8O3.", "answer": "15.9193", "hash": "3cb5d75fd6b22182ab8c53511024e417339030122d21a510501672f817ef2d61", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_196.txt"}
{"question": "Position a point M. Construct a point H at distance M from point 7. Create a regular 7-sided polygon beginning at points H and M, name the additional vertices ['Z', 'S', 'T', 'U', 'X'], and denote the polygon as Q. Create a regular 4-sided polygon beginning at points S and Z, name the additional vertices ['L', 'C9'], and denote the polygon as N. What is the area of polygon N?", "answer": "49.0", "hash": "076a88fe0bf2f066c6d6cf52c4c08be9b42475e4d0feb53d86bac252971859b7", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_761.txt"}
{"question": "Mark a point Y. Construct a point N at distance Y from point 7. Mark the point D that divides the segment from Y to N into two equal parts. Create a regular 4-sided polygon beginning at points Y and D, name the additional vertices ['V', 'H'], and denote the polygon as U. Identify the point I common to both segments segment VH and segment DV. Create a regular 3-sided polygon beginning at points H and I, name the additional vertices ['J7'], and denote the polygon as W8. Find the area of polygon W8.", "answer": "5.3044", "hash": "6f093e2c77760cc7d6eed36f3ea67bf34a86c3846b8e415c6e2b48a554d4b0b0", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_898.txt"}
{"question": "Position a point N. Create a point Z at a distance of N from point 5. Create a line segment U between points N and Z. Create the line J that perpendicularly bisects segment segment NZ. Establish a line segment D from point Z to point N. Create a circle V with its center at point N and radius matching the length of segment segment ZN. Determine the points A and X where circle V intersects line J. Find circle E by reflecting circle V through point A. Determine the radius Z7 of circle E. Compute the value of Z7.", "answer": "5.0", "hash": "4a1308969bbffa49e360e6e25737b4b5b2985f289e9ce6dabd7e5fcdbf8da2d8", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_931.txt"}
{"question": "Construct a point K. Construct a point Q. Construct a regular polygon with 9 sides starting from points K and Q, call the new vertices ['U', 'M', 'Y', 'G', 'S', 'J', 'E'], and label the resulting polygon as T. Compute the angle N8 formed by the rays from point E to points J and U. Find the measure of angle JEU.", "answer": "4.5379", "hash": "a2748619b941559a453aeb42a8731f71d95c77efb0a445ae72d053c6d37b510f", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_492.txt"}
{"question": "Position a point V. Mark a point D such that its distance from point 2 is V. Construct a regular polygon with 9 sides starting from points D and V, call the new vertices ['B', 'G', 'E', 'X', 'I', 'Q', 'P'], and label the resulting polygon as H. Create a regular 9-sided polygon beginning at points B and Q, name the additional vertices ['J5', 'X9', 'F2', 'Y2', 'I7', 'I4', 'M9'], and denote the polygon as F7. Calculate the power E4 of the length of segment segment X9F2 to the exponent 5. Calculate the value of E4.", "answer": "6333.574", "hash": "d5bb7792c121b059e0088c4524cbff84c3ff543a53765bb1596d22898bcb1361", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_287.txt"}
{"question": "Place a point H. Create point O such that it lies 4.9 units from point H in any direction. Establish a line segment D from point O to point H. Draw the perpendicular bisector Z that divides segment segment OH into two equal parts. Place point J on line Z such that it is 4.2 units away from point O. Form segment A joining points O and J. Mark the point L that divides the segment from O to H into two equal parts. Determine point E as the mirror image of point L with segment segment OJ as the mirror. Mark point B on line Z at a distance of 4.5 from point H. Find the measure of angle N6 formed by points L, B, and E. What is the measure of angle LBE?", "answer": "0.9962", "hash": "6795604ca76d39300bb1139991fe75d21a5ef0d15917e023689981cfe5d290cd", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_990.txt"}
{"question": "Place a point X. Mark point N at a distance of 3.3 from point X in an arbitrary direction. Create point I as the reflection of point X across point N. Construct a point W. Establish a circle T with center N and radius equal to the distance from N to I. Create circle R as the reflection of circle T across point W. Find the radius J of circle R. Calculate the power E of measure J to the exponent 2. Calculate the value of E.", "answer": "10.89", "hash": "87dd7ee6ecd631fa8bae04dd67ac21e70d148d03e21cef255196bf76eb34db41", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_952.txt"}
{"question": "Create a point D. Mark a point G such that its distance from point 7 is D. Form segment R joining points G and D. Compute I as the length of segment segment GD raised to the power of 8. Compute the value of I.", "answer": "5764801.0", "hash": "f58a678ad3793531f75d3bad2c9f63551b2c46f98bc3638e633b16e98e46c388", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_406.txt"}
{"question": "Mark a point C. Mark a point S. Create a point W. Create a point V at a distance of W from point 7. Find the midpoint O of points C and S. Construct a regular polygon with 10 sides starting from points V and O, call the new vertices ['H', 'J', 'N', 'K', 'Y', 'V2', 'N7', 'A4'], and label the resulting polygon as F. Calculate the measure of angle M7 with vertex at A4 and sides passing through J and K. Find the measure of angle JA4K.", "answer": "0.6283", "hash": "fc3be1365bbfc35f962f175768067618d5b0297ee2068d8dba32d2b11459032a", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_776.txt"}
{"question": "Place a point V. Mark a point D such that its distance from point 3 is V. Form vector K with initial point V and terminal point D. Find point F by moving point V according to vector K. Construct a regular polygon with 6 sides starting from points D and V, call the new vertices ['L', 'H', 'X', 'P'], and label the resulting polygon as I. Create point Y as the reflection of point P across segment segment LH. Establish a circle Q that passes through each of the points Y, X, and F. Measure the radius C of circle circle YXF. Compute the value of C.", "answer": "5.7236", "hash": "c68e88892ee1ec34154e8173120188e83203de9346a8f9ffd0ba54c2a379a455", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_626.txt"}
{"question": "Mark a point H. Create a point T. Form a line P that goes through points T and H. Construct point K at distance 1.8 from point H in a random direction. Determine point Z by reflecting point H over line P. Construct a regular polygon with 10 sides starting from points K and Z, call the new vertices ['S', 'V3', 'U3', 'S4', 'S2', 'W3', 'M7', 'D2'], and label the resulting polygon as C. Find point O8 such that point S4 is the midpoint of the segment from M7 to O8. Compute the angle F7 formed by the rays from point H to points S2 and O8. Find the measure of angle S2HO8.", "answer": "5.5389", "hash": "4b99ad895ed43a784a9367f376314c6c77dc5fcabba522bbdaf9dd920437ef44", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_27.txt"}
{"question": "Construct a point G. Create a point Q. Determine the point V that is equidistant from points Q and G. Find point J such that point V is the midpoint of the segment from Q to J. Construct a regular polygon with 2 sides starting from points V and J, call the new vertices [], and label the resulting polygon as O. Create a line A through point G that runs in the same direction as segment segment JV. Find point I by reflecting point V over segment segment VJ. Construct point D on line A, at distance 2.8 from point I. Compute the angle N formed by the rays from point I to points D and J. Find the measure of angle DIJ.", "answer": "3.1416", "hash": "be7abc2f8da8357a12e1616ab1672edbe003a1f028926d788a0f95ca4139a83e", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_214.txt"}
{"question": "Construct a point H. Place a point T that is H units away from point 8. Form the perpendicular bisector V of the segment from point T to point H. Construct point N on line V, at distance 3.7 from point T. Establish a circle S with center N and radius equal to the distance from N to T. Find the radius J of circle S. Compute the value of J.", "answer": "5.4489", "hash": "0d51d0a33784c0f72939e8ecb3923924fd967353446133f1f68a89db1ad28d8c", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_585.txt"}
{"question": "Place a point S. Construct a point B at distance S from point 10. Establish a line G passing through both points B and S. Identify the midpoint D of the segment connecting points S and B. Reflect point S across line G, and call the resulting point J. Create a regular 10-sided polygon beginning at points D and J, name the additional vertices ['P', 'L', 'I', 'W', 'N', 'K', 'V', 'C6'], and denote the polygon as X. Compute the angle E1 formed by the rays from point L to points V and C6. Find the measure of angle VLC6.", "answer": "0.3142", "hash": "35f33010a0ab4b4985a32512d6a90b2a38dc64013dd8aae9b74feb42a7423f6b", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_743.txt"}
{"question": "Position a point X. Construct point U at distance 3.3 from point X in a random direction. Measure the distance S between points U and X. Create a circle W with its center at point U and radius equal to S. Reflect circle W across point X, and call the resulting circle V. Locate the point R at which circles V and W cross each other. Find point L such that point X is the midpoint of the segment from U to L. Determine the distance D from point R to point L. Calculate the value of D.", "answer": "3.3", "hash": "03d960420ae45dc174f56765a45fa1484c69584db657237ecb3490d4546ae06e", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_456.txt"}
{"question": "Create a point V. Position a point M. Construct point J at distance 4.9 from point V in a random direction. Construct a regular polygon with 6 sides starting from points M and J, call the new vertices ['E', 'D', 'A', 'H'], and label the resulting polygon as Z. Identify the midpoint U of the segment connecting points E and M. Locate the midpoint H7 between points E and U. Measure the angle T3 formed by points J, M, and H7. Find the measure of angle JMH7.", "answer": "0.5236", "hash": "56fa757ca48d6f7a389d684455d4567f8f4902829a6cbb7a57905ca00cb2879b", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_661.txt"}
{"question": "Place a point B. Place a point M that is B units away from point 3. Create a regular 8-sided polygon beginning at points B and M, name the additional vertices ['H', 'R', 'P', 'V', 'W', 'O'], and denote the polygon as G. Compute M2 as the length of segment segment WO raised to the power of 3. Compute the value of M2.", "answer": "27.0", "hash": "147a68297630aac67d654806eb89e6f396e0f7f8858c6b07717fbb00e8212295", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_315.txt"}
{"question": "Position a point L. Construct point E at distance 2.7 from point L in a random direction. Determine the point C that is equidistant from points L and E. Construct a regular polygon with 8 sides starting from points C and L, call the new vertices ['T', 'R', 'W', 'V', 'H', 'O'], and label the resulting polygon as J. Construct a regular polygon with 5 sides starting from points O and H, call the new vertices ['Z2', 'X8', 'T1'], and label the resulting polygon as B4. What is the area of polygon B4?", "answer": "3.1356", "hash": "4c9da43903d046f9ecb106e66bd2a6e1f8fe6e59b64d35bf3f0d9aa7ea2d2e9d", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_923.txt"}
{"question": "Place a point N. Construct point S at distance 4.5 from point N in a random direction. Find point O such that point N is the midpoint of the segment from S to O. Draw a circle B centered at O that passes through point S. Determine the radius T of circle B. Compute the value of T.", "answer": "9.0", "hash": "82aad5448428c4eb9adf5278cee8232a593ef4e1865fca960808cb352e6e88a7", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_591.txt"}
{"question": "Create a point Q. Place point Y so that it is 3.4 units away from point Q in any direction. Measure the distance J between points Y and Q. Compute the value of J.", "answer": "3.4", "hash": "70a395e2b43949cecbd19d21826ba8459c1102446ca67aa2e3d99827227e49a7", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_189.txt"}
{"question": "Place a point H. Mark a point S such that its distance from point 2 is H. Construct point O as the image of point S when reflected over point H. Construct a regular polygon with 10 sides starting from points H and O, call the new vertices ['D', 'B', 'U', 'P', 'V', 'Z', 'G', 'T'], and label the resulting polygon as C. Find the midpoint T8 of segment segment HO. Measure the angle U6 formed by points T8, D, and O. What is the measure of angle T8DO?", "answer": "0.2063", "hash": "7dfcd3ac4b8321efb517b6340aa0ef316ac610d26f5c02f2f54660f2de8b4c21", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_881.txt"}
{"question": "Place a point Q. Place point Z so that it is 2.1 units away from point Q in any direction. Draw a circle F centered at Z that passes through point Q. Determine the point A that is equidistant from points Q and Z. Find circle Y by reflecting circle F through point A. Compute the value W2 equal to the radius of circle Y. Compute the value of W2.", "answer": "2.1", "hash": "41a7282e5f0ed4af0d6bf04c16c5f8d07b020f723305dfa3860fefc2e09cd3c7", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_345.txt"}
{"question": "Construct a point E. Mark a point O such that its distance from point 5 is E. Construct a circle L with center E passing through point O. Construct ray A starting at point O and passing through point E. Draw a line M passing through point E that is perpendicular to ray A. Find the intersection points Q and J of line M and circle L. Create a line K connecting points Q and E. Construct a point G5 on circle L. Reflect point G5 across line K, and call the resulting point N2. Find the length T1 between points E and N2. Calculate the value of T1.", "answer": "5.0", "hash": "ac98de8efe19fe3a3f9f1d8f30e019ca726b1f92eb0e80156638b16dcf22a78f", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_556.txt"}
{"question": "Position a point Y. Place a point N that is Y units away from point 10. Compute the length P of the straight line from point Y to point N. Compute the value of P.", "answer": "10.0", "hash": "d6fe070d8dcfed3f87d194279cee31d2ee850215f2ee70cd34166dade03b37ba", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_323.txt"}
{"question": "Position a point T. Place a point M that is T units away from point 3. Create a regular 10-sided polygon beginning at points M and T, name the additional vertices ['B', 'F', 'H', 'X', 'C', 'N', 'Y', 'I'], and denote the polygon as J. Form segment B6 joining points N and F. What is the length of segment NF?", "answer": "9.2331", "hash": "0bd596c30e546a500d54dfea6e5defb94fe6aef1629e663e20b7e224d0e01413", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_100.txt"}
{"question": "Construct a point M. Construct point W at distance 2.2 from point M in a random direction. Construct point Q as the image of point W when reflected over point M. Compute the length T of the straight line from point W to point Q. Compute the value of T.", "answer": "4.4", "hash": "33c1685555b6c9bdf6a9aada4150f9b472fec9f95700e9f7809d57f16b122dfa", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_517.txt"}
{"question": "Place a point G. Position point A at a distance of 1.9 from point G, in whichever direction you choose. Create a regular 4-sided polygon beginning at points A and G, name the additional vertices ['R', 'V'], and denote the polygon as O. Determine point K as the mirror image of point V with segment segment GR as the mirror. Draw a line P passing through point K that is parallel to segment segment AG. Mark point E on line P at a distance of 3.5 from point G. Find the measure of angle M9 formed by points E, A, and R. What is the measure of angle EAR?", "answer": "0.4471", "hash": "396890108dcbe57a54ccc1eda40213eff8aef247193728743e279ffd6d4a328b", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_329.txt"}
{"question": "Create a point O. Create a point E at a distance of O from point 7. Position a point A so that it is exactly E units from point 7. Find the length B between points A and E. Calculate the value of B.", "answer": "7.0", "hash": "dc7313ac12b34f0eaa3231dcb213deab7e54fd1784c8f256b88fdc63216449da", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_320.txt"}
{"question": "Construct a point Q. Mark a point R such that its distance from point 6 is Q. Create a regular 5-sided polygon beginning at points R and Q, name the additional vertices ['W', 'O', 'Y'], and denote the polygon as M. Measure the distance Q5 between points Q and O. Calculate the value of Q5.", "answer": "9.7082", "hash": "4b579b85c8c67155ece74cc22cc3b082dc0b92c8a299fd3173ba5cd6d8e60281", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_548.txt"}
{"question": "Construct a point U. Mark point F at a distance of 1.7 from point U in an arbitrary direction. Create vector W directed from point F to point U. Determine point A as the image of point F when translated by vector W. Create a regular 10-sided polygon beginning at points A and F, name the additional vertices ['X4', 'H7', 'H2', 'Z6', 'W1', 'R9', 'O7', 'B6'], and denote the polygon as X. Draw a line segment A1 connecting points H7 and X4. Find the length of segment H7X4.", "answer": "1.7", "hash": "636ae3db5e09306ca399012c8953c78dd2f44a3037fae9bd8ac9bbaf0a1cc1e0", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_993.txt"}
{"question": "Create a point A. Mark point F at a distance of 2.1 from point A in an arbitrary direction. Construct a circle I with center A passing through point F. Position a point K somewhere on circle I. Find point J by inverting point K in circle I. Draw a line segment V connecting points A and J. What is the length of segment AJ?", "answer": "2.1", "hash": "3a29fe739af92da24dc1bd0d31553832a305e4489e225527da65d555c830c067", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_265.txt"}
{"question": "Position a point H. Place a point J that is H units away from point 8. Create a regular 6-sided polygon beginning at points J and H, name the additional vertices ['K', 'N', 'M', 'Q'], and denote the polygon as T. Calculate the power Z of the length of segment segment NM to the exponent 8. Compute the value of Z.", "answer": "16777216.0", "hash": "d1019f587f831eca5b024177dda7f6937b9bf12464669f0d6322a9f76d740bb3", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_226.txt"}
{"question": "Create a point K. Mark point R at a distance of 1.6 from point K in an arbitrary direction. Find point I such that point K is the midpoint of the segment from R to I. Find point T such that point I is the midpoint of the segment from K to T. Create a regular 6-sided polygon beginning at points T and K, name the additional vertices ['S', 'X', 'U', 'E'], and denote the polygon as H. Determine the area F of polygon H. Compute L7 as measure F raised to the power of 2. Compute the value of L7.", "answer": "707.7888", "hash": "fb3d2653e818d8637391d9934e9fc26a7e884992c0f610f9e644833647417a51", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_501.txt"}
{"question": "Place a point O. Create a point F at a distance of O from point 1. Identify the midpoint C of the segment connecting points O and F. Create a regular 2-sided polygon beginning at points F and C, name the additional vertices [], and denote the polygon as L. Establish a line R through point F that is parallel to segment segment CF. Create point U as the reflection of point C across line R. Determine the distance X from point O to point U. Calculate the value of X.", "answer": "0.5", "hash": "98f51f24783fa28342a9916bc5e51cba889aa6e587145f714da75f5d10b309fc", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_981.txt"}
{"question": "Position a point R. Position a point O so that it is exactly R units from point 3. Construct a line N through points R and O. Determine point W by reflecting point O over line N. Establish a circle A with center R and radius equal to the distance from R to W. Compute the value V equal to the radius of circle A. Calculate the value of V.", "answer": "3.0", "hash": "a7f650e058c2fdef02f65a8e9f8cf863f5b1bbc45b3c6946e56198c1cbd94ff4", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_592.txt"}
{"question": "Mark a point G. Construct a point U at distance G from point 7. Establish a line N passing through both points G and U. Construct a circle T with center U passing through point G. Locate the points R and V at which circle T crosses line N. Construct a regular polygon with 7 sides starting from points U and R, call the new vertices ['H', 'B', 'I', 'S', 'M'], and label the resulting polygon as E. Compute the angle S4 formed by the rays from point M to points U and H. Find the measure of angle UMH.", "answer": "0.8976", "hash": "b15cf025c7e0cd83dedb2b0e0a90afd59970a2db97e02a2e716b10073cf2b8b7", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_328.txt"}
{"question": "Mark a point B. Construct a point M at distance B from point 2. Measure the distance A between points M and B. Calculate the value of A.", "answer": "2.0", "hash": "e07dff5a60d24ab307503f49ff89b8a558cd0b4cd970db6cf9937029c9c9b627", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_225.txt"}
{"question": "Construct a point P. Position a point H. Identify the midpoint C of the segment connecting points P and H. Form segment M joining points C and P. Determine point F as the mirror image of point P with segment segment CP as the mirror. Draw the perpendicular bisector L of the line segment connecting points C and F. Identify the point N common to both line L and segment segment CP. Compute the angle E formed by the rays from point N to points C and F. Find the measure of angle CNF.", "answer": "3.1416", "hash": "e315d584eb66554fc498d1513cf1e8fcd02bf6193b2b4a6716b0576bd6798f01", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_101.txt"}
{"question": "Mark a point J. Mark a point Q such that its distance from point 5 is J. Construct a point I at distance J from point 3. Find the length K between points J and I. Establish a circle F with center point Q and radius measuring K units. Find the radius G of circle F. Calculate the value of G.", "answer": "3.0", "hash": "1a5da6b7fbd42ca73c1497416473e7ded8ff9b30c11d34a5d3ba9bca25cd3e49", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_90.txt"}
{"question": "Mark a point T. Place a point N that is T units away from point 6. Create a regular 8-sided polygon beginning at points T and N, name the additional vertices ['O', 'Y', 'X', 'G', 'D', 'K'], and denote the polygon as B. Create a circle R with its center at point K and radius matching the length of segment segment GD. Determine the radius P2 of circle R. Calculate the value of P2.", "answer": "6.0", "hash": "2580ca83f2c21b2500dc7b4c8cd6e796d67aec295c463f02b5f3dacf371ca35b", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_176.txt"}
{"question": "Mark a point F. Construct point H at distance 1.8 from point F in a random direction. Place point G so that it is 4.4 units away from point H in any direction. Find the midpoint E of points H and F. Establish a line U passing through both points G and E. Create a line L through point H that forms a right angle with line U. Determine the point S where lines U and L intersect. Draw a circle A that passes through the three points S, G, and H. Determine the radius X of circle circle SGH. Compute the value of X.", "answer": "2.2", "hash": "b4f73cd1f2e797334d1e6880b3733c08ff3c3f9b01a6af0c55dab27ad986e62d", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_316.txt"}
{"question": "Place a point N. Place point K so that it is 3.3 units away from point N in any direction. Construct the perpendicular bisector U of points N and K. Create point X on line U so that its distance from point N is 3.3. Position point L on line U, exactly 4.7 units away from point X. Find the midpoint P of points L and K. Create a regular 8-sided polygon beginning at points L and P, name the additional vertices ['F5', 'N7', 'L6', 'G3', 'W9', 'Y7'], and denote the polygon as E5. What is the area of polygon E5?", "answer": "80.5412", "hash": "5755d4155b7bdd8fd35ce89cbd71d6a2b00dfee4361a6a12ebe39a3bd2e86d6d", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_88.txt"}
{"question": "Construct a point J. Mark point Q at a distance of 3.8 from point J in an arbitrary direction. Define vector H starting at point J and ending at point Q. Construct point N by shifting point Q in the direction and magnitude of vector H. Construct a regular polygon with 3 sides starting from points N and Q, call the new vertices ['W'], and label the resulting polygon as O. Compute L as the length of segment segment QW raised to the power of 3. Compute the value of L.", "answer": "54.872", "hash": "4cf07348f56a9649624f7139215cfa5ab4f731ad895bef833f936352915eb1a4", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_210.txt"}
{"question": "Create a point C. Construct a point R at distance C from point 2. Determine point Q by reflecting point C through point R. Compute the length P of the straight line from point R to point Q. Calculate the value of P.", "answer": "2.0", "hash": "c48083002e879c82b3b3b7651d7ad8a10e1fe06481f50b6553243394e4b7b117", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_174.txt"}
{"question": "Position a point F. Create point P such that it lies 2.1 units from point F in any direction. Create a regular 9-sided polygon beginning at points F and P, name the additional vertices ['M', 'K', 'Y', 'U', 'I', 'A', 'E'], and denote the polygon as J. Measure the distance Q8 between points P and A. Compute the value of Q8.", "answer": "5.3174", "hash": "9623afe12bfb244c37f04ba3fdd432596264decc1d146ad8e6732cd8a697a93e", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_511.txt"}
{"question": "Position a point D. Mark a point K. Construct a regular polygon with 9 sides starting from points K and D, call the new vertices ['F', 'L', 'W', 'X', 'T', 'Q', 'A'], and label the resulting polygon as N. Find point I2 such that point D is the midpoint of the segment from K to I2. Calculate the measure of angle J1 with vertex at L and sides passing through I2 and T. What is the measure of angle I2LT?", "answer": "4.3263", "hash": "c6abc403447805f4a4b2ed05929762f44e7a237f0f4af6c7ba818a4d2cc832c3", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_960.txt"}
{"question": "Place a point M. Place a point W that is M units away from point 3. Create a regular 9-sided polygon beginning at points W and M, name the additional vertices ['Q', 'X', 'S', 'K', 'C', 'A', 'D'], and denote the polygon as I. Determine the angle Z created by the three points K, A, and C. Find the measure of angle KAC.", "answer": "0.3491", "hash": "8ed172e93c56cb8348e144d054cfd79cfb7751f6d01cfd3b52acc33354fab9d3", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_400.txt"}
{"question": "Place a point W. Position point P at a distance of 4.5 from point W, in whichever direction you choose. Establish a line segment X from point P to point W. Calculate the power J of the length of segment segment PW to the exponent 1. Compute the value of J.", "answer": "4.5", "hash": "61f1af3220eb94f0ef9e58490684b9d141c75afbdd2558efce11b6312d5394e0", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_242.txt"}
{"question": "Position a point M. Position point L at a distance of 4.9 from point M, in whichever direction you choose. Construct a regular polygon with 7 sides starting from points L and M, call the new vertices ['X', 'G', 'U', 'V', 'I'], and label the resulting polygon as O. Create point K as the reflection of point X across point U. Mark the point R7 where segments segment IL and segment LM meet. Compute the angle R6 formed by the rays from point K to points M and R7. What is the measure of angle MKR7?", "answer": "6.031", "hash": "782ef348e4bd83b90d23b5d4350b8507d9a65b9b9aa9d61740eb8d1487e39bf0", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_458.txt"}
{"question": "Create a point O. Position point A at a distance of 4.2 from point O, in whichever direction you choose. Reflect point O across point A, and call the resulting point V. Construct a regular polygon with 9 sides starting from points A and O, call the new vertices ['Z', 'Y', 'C', 'Q', 'K', 'J', 'I'], and label the resulting polygon as U. Draw a line I6 that passes through points C and K. Place point V2 on line I6 such that it is 3.2 units away from point Z. Create a regular 9-sided polygon beginning at points V2 and V, name the additional vertices ['V7', 'Q1', 'Q2', 'O2', 'Y5', 'J4', 'A6'], and denote the polygon as W5. What is the area of polygon W5?", "answer": "1116.0694", "hash": "ac691ddf7f8b588e6c14f307a04794a6f4b648dd0147f97d7f4af23c31d29b23", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_47.txt"}
{"question": "Position a point Z. Place point V so that it is 4.3 units away from point Z in any direction. Determine the distance J from point V to point Z. Draw a circle U centered at V with a radius of J units. Create a line segment K between points Z and V. Create the line A that perpendicularly bisects segment segment ZV. Find the intersection points W and B of circle U and line A. Create a regular 5-sided polygon beginning at points Z and B, name the additional vertices ['E8', 'L2', 'M6'], and denote the polygon as T. Compute Z1 as the length of segment segment E8L2 raised to the power of 9. Compute the value of Z1.", "answer": "502592.6119", "hash": "8338d01577876c5d02ccf4a6bbdc89389319992ef2e5bb8a8fa8dbd53235e3d9", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_497.txt"}
{"question": "Place a point I. Place a point G that is I units away from point 4. Create a regular 7-sided polygon beginning at points G and I, name the additional vertices ['U', 'L', 'T', 'J', 'Z'], and denote the polygon as O. Create a regular 5-sided polygon beginning at points I and Z, name the additional vertices ['P9', 'U8', 'Z3'], and denote the polygon as J1. Find the area of polygon J1.", "answer": "89.3817", "hash": "7186474a32e0d8f588eb10f153f06fbecfc544932e26b07962259bb2dc7e2447", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_338.txt"}
{"question": "Construct a point R. Create a point L at a distance of R from point 2. Create a circle W with its center at R and containing point L on its circumference. Construct a regular polygon with 5 sides starting from points R and L, call the new vertices ['M', 'H', 'I'], and label the resulting polygon as E. Construct a circle D with center M passing through point H. Identify the points O and S common to both circles W and D. Calculate the measure of angle Z4 with vertex at L and sides passing through S and H. Find the measure of angle SLH.", "answer": "5.969", "hash": "dac2af548e1bff33c8f0be8512e200e7cbc555948d641d9a4f8b6fb1814de7ec", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_392.txt"}
{"question": "Position a point G. Construct a point U at distance G from point 2. Construct point R at distance 2.7 from point U in a random direction. Compute the length L of the straight line from point U to point R. Compute O as measure L raised to the power of 2. Calculate the value of O.", "answer": "7.29", "hash": "0e655323e70f11ee1150bf7db5b49dd200db01c9ec100f94811c47ed81051d9d", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_680.txt"}
{"question": "Construct a point G. Compute Q as the sum of measures 4.9 and 2.2. Mark point M at a distance of 3.0 from point G in an arbitrary direction. Determine the distance H from point G to point M. Calculate the ratio R of measure H to measure Q. Calculate the value of R.", "answer": "0.4225", "hash": "1f4e6bf381284f89d17acd486fa8c2453a0be9aa34b5fbc60261036c8b800359", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_384.txt"}
{"question": "Mark a point L. Place a point K that is L units away from point 1. Form segment V joining points L and K. Determine the point G that divides segment segment LK into two equal parts. Determine point T as the mirror image of point K with segment segment LK as the mirror. Establish vector N pointing from point K toward point L. Find the midpoint U of points T and L. Locate the midpoint B between points K and U. Construct point S by shifting point U in the direction and magnitude of vector N. Determine the angle F6 created by the three points S, G, and B. Find the measure of angle SGB.", "answer": "3.1416", "hash": "e60b9fe1d82781c18d38209841dfd4c6fddf46bd3862e670369a0e00b25315f0", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_262.txt"}
{"question": "Mark a point P. Place point R so that it is 1.4 units away from point P in any direction. Create the line H that perpendicularly bisects the segment between points R and P. Create point J as the reflection of point P across point R. Construct a line D through point R parallel to line H. Create point K as the reflection of point P across line D. Determine the point W that is equidistant from points J and K. Identify the midpoint G of the segment connecting points P and W. Establish a line segment T8 from point K to point G. What is the length of segment KG?", "answer": "1.4", "hash": "927ccf204e9427458ae59d4a8df878e44ab0de932258d2ed432e7d1e3989f66f", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_29.txt"}
{"question": "Construct a point M. Construct point J at distance 2.4 from point M in a random direction. Draw a circle S centered at M that passes through point J. Designate point Y as the center of circle S. Construct a regular polygon with 8 sides starting from points J and Y, call the new vertices ['C', 'R', 'Z', 'F', 'B', 'K'], and label the resulting polygon as L. Identify the point E at the middle of segment segment BK. Establish a line segment X9 from point F to point E. Find the length of segment FE.", "answer": "3.3575", "hash": "8ec8a6119f198409bdae18063926d3a522bceb0b373c7de1af547297231de870", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_815.txt"}
{"question": "Mark a point Y. Mark point V at a distance of 3.3 from point Y in an arbitrary direction. Construct a regular polygon with 5 sides starting from points V and Y, call the new vertices ['H', 'R', 'F'], and label the resulting polygon as P. Construct point O as the image of point V when reflected across segment segment HR. Compute the length E of the straight line from point O to point H. Compute the value of E.", "answer": "5.3395", "hash": "b075478249f69d974d3b30f592cbf2629f579c39f1a2e3616e5a1605b69c5136", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_301.txt"}
{"question": "Create a point T. Create a point N. Construct a regular polygon with 1 sides starting from points N and T, call the new vertices ['Q'], and label the resulting polygon as Z. Construct a regular polygon with 3 sides starting from points T and N, call the new vertices ['J'], and label the resulting polygon as S. Calculate the power U of the length of segment segment NN to the exponent 1. Create a regular 6-sided polygon beginning at points J and N, name the additional vertices ['P', 'B', 'N6', 'Q4'], and denote the polygon as X. Construct a regular polygon with 3 sides starting from points Q4 and T, call the new vertices ['S7'], and label the resulting polygon as O5. Form a circle G6 centered at T with a distance of U from center to circumference. Construct point Q3 as the image of point Q4 when reflected over point S7. Designate point M3 as the center of circle G6. Determine the angle M6 created by the three points J, Q3, and M3. Find the measure of angle JQ3M3.", "answer": "0.281", "hash": "764f0dd0dfc4fcd0f6dfd35e305cfbf71a87206b21253a8c05f1cf27a8f7da60", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_506.txt"}
{"question": "Create a point S. Mark a point W such that its distance from point 2 is S. Create a regular 4-sided polygon beginning at points W and S, name the additional vertices ['U', 'A'], and denote the polygon as F. Reflect point S across segment segment AW, and call the resulting point O. Determine the distance L from point A to point W. Establish a circle X with center point S and radius measuring L units. Mark point D as the center of circle X. Create a regular 4-sided polygon beginning at points O and S, name the additional vertices ['B2', 'P4'], and denote the polygon as E8. Measure the angle M4 formed by points D, O, and P4. What is the measure of angle DOP4?", "answer": "1.5708", "hash": "2558eff917cc665fffd3629bacbf7cfe37d837fde71b652378936b1e3a3d66bc", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_57.txt"}
{"question": "Place a point Z. Construct a point P at distance Z from point 6. Create a regular 3-sided polygon beginning at points Z and P, name the additional vertices ['O'], and denote the polygon as W. Find the area of polygon W.", "answer": "15.5885", "hash": "cdc00881b44eb83fdd41728eed7dae951f14405291696becfabce9bca2d14deb", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_354.txt"}
{"question": "Construct a point V. Place a point L. Position point G at a distance of 4.0 from point V, in whichever direction you choose. Construct a line B through points G and L. Construct a point Z at distance L from point 5. Draw a circle H that passes through the three points Z, G, and V. Position a point X so that it is exactly G units from point 2. Identify the points I and Q common to both circle circle ZGV and line B. Draw a line segment D connecting points Q and X. What is the length of segment QX?", "answer": "2.0", "hash": "0087e14aa584bb3c87bbd4efef2605fee0afc145c027800ad80b2add0005e245", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_686.txt"}
{"question": "Mark a point K. Create a point I. Construct a line O through points K and I. Mark point V on line O at a distance of 2.5 from point K. Measure the distance Q between points K and V. Calculate the value of Q.", "answer": "2.5", "hash": "ef56731c7e915831dca4e5e5191d95c1d581a789723f339cbd3273254e075991", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_357.txt"}
{"question": "Mark a point X. Place point N so that it is 2.9 units away from point X in any direction. Draw a line S that passes through points N and X. Place point A on line S such that it is 3.9 units away from point X. Construct a circle Q with center A passing through point N. Find the radius U of circle Q. Compute the value of U.", "answer": "6.8", "hash": "be5ed4c4c418c78bee6c23f2c6a795e851edce8c38d33d3105b66bc7ceb9df04", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_51.txt"}
{"question": "Position a point D. Place a point Z that is D units away from point 9. Construct a regular polygon with 10 sides starting from points Z and D, call the new vertices ['Y', 'K', 'U', 'X', 'A', 'P', 'Q', 'I'], and label the resulting polygon as C. Create a circle W with its center at point Y and radius matching the length of segment segment UX. Compute the value T equal to the radius of circle W. Calculate the value of T.", "answer": "9.0", "hash": "17fa9b247bde752babb0420299dad84dad9f5bf747530272296c7f5d6776abbf", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_901.txt"}
{"question": "Position a point T. Create point C such that it lies 4.3 units from point T in any direction. Create point P as the reflection of point T across point C. Construct the angle bisector R of angle CTP. Create a regular 9-sided polygon beginning at points C and T, name the additional vertices ['J', 'Q', 'F', 'M6', 'H9', 'Y6', 'F4'], and denote the polygon as X. Create ray H2 originating from point M6 and extending through point C. Draw a circle L1 that passes through the three points Y6, F, and P. Locate the point T8 at which line R crosses ray H2. Mark the points Q9 and U6 where line R meets circle circle Y6FP. Measure the distance L4 between points Q9 and T8. Calculate the value of L4.", "answer": "4.3", "hash": "d930446debfe0a8bdb6673b176859223e0c3683babb455a340317029fe83d505", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_4.txt"}
{"question": "Place a point E. Mark a point T such that its distance from point 9 is E. Determine point K by reflecting point T through point E. Determine point S by reflecting point T through point K. Construct segment W from point K to point S. Compute R as the length of segment segment KS raised to the power of 6. Calculate the value of R.", "answer": "34012224.0", "hash": "ff8fb410f098235e5551668281cd0ddaa9707319ae46ef4f79529becdd0525e8", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_828.txt"}
{"question": "Position a point Y. Position a point L so that it is exactly Y units from point 3. Determine point K by reflecting point Y through point L. Create a regular 9-sided polygon beginning at points Y and K, name the additional vertices ['F5', 'Y2', 'C7', 'J5', 'F8', 'G7', 'P4'], and denote the polygon as S. Compute F1 as the length of segment segment F8G7 raised to the power of 7. Calculate the value of F1.", "answer": "279936.0", "hash": "eb6294965470de873d9ed37cf85052adde69bdd8a044de963e1c49525193f3e2", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_46.txt"}
{"question": "Construct a point G. Create a point J at a distance of G from point 5. Create a regular 9-sided polygon beginning at points G and J, name the additional vertices ['C9', 'A3', 'J6', 'V6', 'A5', 'U5', 'F7'], and denote the polygon as E. Measure the angle U2 formed by points G, J6, and A5. Find the measure of angle GJ6A5.", "answer": "5.236", "hash": "e348c9632b11bf77c681273cf9e7455fa1679b68cc5431b63ef1642f2227d544", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_245.txt"}
{"question": "Mark a point L. Place a point W that is L units away from point 6. Identify the midpoint U of the segment connecting points W and L. Form a circle F centered at point W such that point U lies on it. Find circle Q by reflecting circle F through point W. Designate point N as the center of circle F. Construct segment G from point U to point N. Draw a line P passing through point N that is parallel to segment segment UN. Construct circle X as the image of circle Q when reflected across line P. Construct a point R on circle X. Create a line segment C1 between points R and N. What is the length of segment RN?", "answer": "3.0", "hash": "3a18c4b3b7857f7cd67228840f3e2099eabb1112409215622128f57aec2dce8e", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_188.txt"}
{"question": "Construct a point X. Create a point H at a distance of X from point 4. Find the length F between points X and H. Establish a circle U with center point H and radius measuring F units. Construct point J as the image of point X under inversion in circle U. Compute the length B of the straight line from point H to point J. Compute the value of B.", "answer": "4.0", "hash": "89c33bc8ec8ac5e57f1b496085f8adc9eedc64ff5371395c60b06c0a03d22100", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_624.txt"}
{"question": "Create a point A. Create point Y such that it lies 2.3 units from point A in any direction. Position a point H so that it is exactly Y units from point 2. Construct a regular polygon with 4 sides starting from points H and Y, call the new vertices ['T', 'M'], and label the resulting polygon as B. Calculate the area R of polygon B. Compute the value of R.", "answer": "4.0", "hash": "328ef68133e9f2086756cfd7748c1edd3fde8ec267fe83dcbfaefecf95462f9a", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_398.txt"}
{"question": "Place a point G. Create point D such that it lies 1.5 units from point G in any direction. Calculate the sum I of measures 1.6 and 4.9. Create a regular 9-sided polygon beginning at points D and G, name the additional vertices ['Z2', 'Q9', 'M9', 'R3', 'Y5', 'Q4', 'Q2'], and denote the polygon as Q. Compute W8 as the length of segment segment Q4Q2 raised to the power of 8. Calculate the ratio U4 of measure W8 to measure I. Compute the value of U4.", "answer": "3.9429", "hash": "e0e22fc3c1571f82bb8cd0ad3ed300cfcaf9be9f394ee958e24bfa1a6ad6fd22", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_389.txt"}
{"question": "Place a point V. Place point K so that it is 3.4 units away from point V in any direction. Construct a regular polygon with 3 sides starting from points K and V, call the new vertices ['A'], and label the resulting polygon as H. Mark the point E where segments segment AK and segment VA meet. Create point T as the reflection of point E across segment segment KV. Create a line segment F between points T and A. What is the length of segment TA?", "answer": "5.889", "hash": "f5409852204a722ee12099c2fda32f8d0250a672cc684c9f250658d9fe8c34b0", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_816.txt"}
{"question": "Construct a point R. Position a point N so that it is exactly R units from point 2. Construct a regular polygon with 5 sides starting from points N and R, call the new vertices ['I', 'U', 'S'], and label the resulting polygon as F. Calculate the power W of the length of segment segment US to the exponent 8. Calculate the value of W.", "answer": "256.0", "hash": "008256c96b0851f54bf58cc7e2808088bc951fcdb45706677475b8397d31ae50", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_190.txt"}
{"question": "Place a point E. Mark point B at a distance of 4.2 from point E in an arbitrary direction. Create a line segment H between points E and B. Find the length of segment EB.", "answer": "4.2", "hash": "e7840d974091a250711edc725ade274ec5082c61211be486308d36b5323a460e", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_70.txt"}
{"question": "Create a point G. Construct point F at distance 1.5 from point G in a random direction. Find point H such that point G is the midpoint of the segment from F to H. Construct a regular polygon with 3 sides starting from points G and F, call the new vertices ['T'], and label the resulting polygon as V. Create point P as the reflection of point T across point F. Measure the angle U formed by points F, H, and P. What is the measure of angle FHP?", "answer": "5.9497", "hash": "679b34a49bc2d869dd290369c9d816c1ca4c60218469ed460f0a007c6270dd5a", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_202.txt"}
{"question": "Calculate the sum S3 of measures 1.8 and 2.9. Calculate the value of S3.", "answer": "4.7", "hash": "e82aece660cd09e7849dd9ed68d75c93435ed4fbab85e33ca69db55e820f4389", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_105.txt"}
{"question": "Construct a point H. Position a point J so that it is exactly H units from point 5. Construct a regular polygon with 9 sides starting from points H and J, call the new vertices ['F', 'T', 'Z', 'A', 'Y', 'D', 'W'], and label the resulting polygon as G. Find the midpoint X of segment segment JF. Draw a circle H8 centered at X that passes through point H. Measure the radius D6 of circle H8. Compute the value of D6.", "answer": "7.0994", "hash": "8c46debc558e9d16dd79e81427baa8df4b0ac63dfade022421993aa781481adb", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_440.txt"}
{"question": "Position a point O. Construct point N at distance 4.4 from point O in a random direction. Mark point V at a distance of 2.8 from point N in an arbitrary direction. Determine the distance A from point N to point V. Establish a circle X with center point O and radius measuring A units. Measure the radius U1 of circle X. Calculate the value of U1.", "answer": "2.8", "hash": "c4efa61b83b2fee79aceea8325d20b47c7e69262c2763c21a634bb78121f8b3c", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_728.txt"}
{"question": "Construct a point O. Position a point D so that it is exactly O units from point 3. Create a point N. Mark point J at a distance of 2.6 from point D in an arbitrary direction. Construct a point W. Measure the angle K formed by points D, N, and J. Construct point U by turning point W through angle angle DNJ around the fixed point J. Construct point X at distance 4.0 from point U in a random direction. Measure the distance C between points U and X. Calculate the value of C.", "answer": "4.0", "hash": "cb92a83ed4dfcefec8dd3c6904e57b6838718026b31e5828689745906cca54ef", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_1.txt"}
{"question": "Mark a point H. Create a point P at a distance of H from point 1. Find the length G between points P and H. Find the midpoint Y of points H and P. Form a circle E centered at Y with a distance of G from center to circumference. Compute the value Q equal to the radius of circle E. Calculate the value of Q.", "answer": "1.0", "hash": "d8ef11b74b9f8afa34926ab3fec0274f446e50581a91b8c9f6a70bbc2d3c0e53", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_605.txt"}
{"question": "Place a point H. Create point W such that it lies 2.3 units from point H in any direction. Draw a line segment M connecting points W and H. Compute G as the length of segment segment WH raised to the power of 4. Calculate the value of G.", "answer": "27.9841", "hash": "1e302794d7970bca7e364661fbd18abe9bac2b50044f681e6d951b3343cdbb2a", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_620.txt"}
{"question": "Construct a point B. Create point A such that it lies 4.2 units from point B in any direction. Construct a regular polygon with 7 sides starting from points B and A, call the new vertices ['L', 'F', 'S', 'Z', 'H'], and label the resulting polygon as M. Create a regular 7-sided polygon beginning at points H and L, name the additional vertices ['S7', 'J4', 'Y5', 'D7', 'J9'], and denote the polygon as T5. Find the area of polygon T5.", "answer": "323.6468", "hash": "aa6846ec385828543e495c39f1a813ad52f0f380e3e5217a497b598db1a8d91b", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_564.txt"}
{"question": "Position a point W. Place point E so that it is 1.1 units away from point W in any direction. Create a regular 10-sided polygon beginning at points W and E, name the additional vertices ['L', 'C', 'X', 'B', 'F', 'O', 'K', 'D'], and denote the polygon as Q. Create a regular 9-sided polygon beginning at points X and E, name the additional vertices ['F6', 'R1', 'X7', 'R6', 'G4', 'V4', 'Y3'], and denote the polygon as S1. What is the area of polygon S1?", "answer": "51.2687", "hash": "63d6afe46d40b5a43af2c7a6769e19331cf60d152c7ae874ed92dd9aefbc4a61", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_909.txt"}
{"question": "Create a point Q. Place point L so that it is 3.1 units away from point Q in any direction. Create a regular 8-sided polygon beginning at points Q and L, name the additional vertices ['Y', 'I', 'F', 'C', 'S', 'K'], and denote the polygon as M. Draw the perpendicular bisector W of the line segment connecting points Q and I. Mark point B on line W at a distance of 5.0 from point F. Form a circle G8 centered at point B such that point L lies on it. Designate point L5 as the center of circle G8. Create a regular 7-sided polygon beginning at points K and L5, name the additional vertices ['V5', 'W3', 'L8', 'D8', 'E4'], and denote the polygon as S4. Find the area of polygon S4.", "answer": "141.7327", "hash": "2ddf5e7b33759d9da37e44f4c7a15ca7d01a471e847e92a4e640adbd3851352c", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_107.txt"}
{"question": "Position a point V. Create a point J at a distance of V from point 4. Create a circle L with its center at J and containing point V on its circumference. Construct a point E on circle L. Draw the perpendicular bisector M of the line segment connecting points V and E. Find circle S by reflecting circle L over line M. Find the radius X of circle S. Compute the value of X.", "answer": "4.0", "hash": "ce66e39fea0a4e61849768825fb60110b4d9f5cd9d5198f5a659075a3460dd14", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_543.txt"}
{"question": "Place a point Y. Place point G so that it is 1.2 units away from point Y in any direction. Create a regular 5-sided polygon beginning at points Y and G, name the additional vertices ['U', 'L', 'C'], and denote the polygon as F. What is the area of polygon F?", "answer": "2.4775", "hash": "d6edba91db0e00dc78b17efba90e87ea1e4e5548f3179098be52801a96d67da3", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_500.txt"}
{"question": "Place a point N. Create a point J. Draw ray W with endpoint at J that passes through point N. Construct a regular polygon with 3 sides starting from points N and J, call the new vertices ['L'], and label the resulting polygon as E. Construct a regular polygon with 4 sides starting from points L and J, call the new vertices ['H', 'A'], and label the resulting polygon as P. Mark the point B that divides the segment from N to A into two equal parts. Establish a line X through point J that runs parallel to ray W. Reflect point L across line X, and call the resulting point L1. Calculate the measure of angle O7 with vertex at J and sides passing through L1 and B. What is the measure of angle L1JB?", "answer": "4.0997", "hash": "8adbc40c503b3f7fc82d265a23146af529d7dcb782b96ccc68dd86133b770873", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_991.txt"}
{"question": "Place a point L. Position a point F so that it is exactly L units from point 6. Create a regular 10-sided polygon beginning at points F and L, name the additional vertices ['W', 'X', 'Q', 'E', 'K', 'R', 'D', 'S'], and denote the polygon as I. Draw a circle B1 that passes through the three points S, L, and K. Define point D6 to be the center of circle circle SLK. Measure the angle I1 formed by points W, D6, and X. What is the measure of angle WD6X?", "answer": "0.6283", "hash": "84dcaa0981eb4ecb7ecbb584f843a69de5f90b1ca8256569396977b213a8a7df", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_509.txt"}
{"question": "Compute B as the sum of measures 3.3 and 3.2. Calculate the value of B.", "answer": "6.5", "hash": "579004a6e34d3fb14213d1bf05dde6fb0715fbdf21ed543718cb91735eee6645", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_971.txt"}
{"question": "Construct a point L. Create a point C at a distance of L from point 10. Find the midpoint Q of points C and L. Create a regular 5-sided polygon beginning at points L and Q, name the additional vertices ['H', 'B', 'E'], and denote the polygon as N. Compute W as the length of segment segment BE raised to the power of 7. Calculate the value of W.", "answer": "78125.0", "hash": "f0826e99b9cccd3a20a19c3dcddd8b6201e9eb9cb16a37a4513ea1684a4697e5", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_83.txt"}
{"question": "Mark a point O. Mark a point M such that its distance from point 6 is O. Create a regular 5-sided polygon beginning at points O and M, name the additional vertices ['Z8', 'M1', 'T3'], and denote the polygon as Z. Determine the distance H4 from point T3 to point Z8. Calculate the value of H4.", "answer": "9.7082", "hash": "b45e50a3315146b48ee748fcfdd6fc649f0a51ccf25e692e8cc03d64fe56beb7", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_290.txt"}
{"question": "Create a point X. Construct point C at distance 4.1 from point X in a random direction. Mark the point K that divides the segment from C to X into two equal parts. Form ray L with its vertex at K and passing through point X. Establish a line A through point X that is orthogonal to ray L. Create point Y on line A so that its distance from point C is 4.9. Compute the length W of the straight line from point Y to point C. Compute T as measure W raised to the power of 2. Calculate the value of T.", "answer": "40.82", "hash": "646b824dd5ef860386e1b45954b867c9058dfa20627d8fd623b7ea3064123984", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_344.txt"}
{"question": "Position a point O. Mark point B at a distance of 2.9 from point O in an arbitrary direction. Form the perpendicular bisector S of the segment from point B to point O. Create point Y as the reflection of point O across line S. Find point H such that point Y is the midpoint of the segment from B to H. Construct point C on line S, at distance 1.6 from point H. Find point Q such that point Y is the midpoint of the segment from C to Q. Measure the distance W between points Y and Q. Calculate the power X of measure W to the exponent 2. Compute the value of X.", "answer": "4.6625", "hash": "2d859489a2ba036a0f419f2870dbed99df0d50adf8537732d7e33e12ffc7e65c", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_891.txt"}
{"question": "Mark a point J. Place point C so that it is 4.3 units away from point J in any direction. Form a circle I centered at point J such that point C lies on it. Compute the value P equal to the radius of circle I. Form segment A joining points C and J. Establish the line E that is perpendicular to segment segment CJ and passes through its midpoint. Create a point Q that lies on circle I. Determine line T as the mirror image of line E with point Q as the center of reflection. Create point R as the reflection of point Q across line T. Construct a circle D with center R and radius P. Find the radius U7 of circle D. Calculate the value of U7.", "answer": "4.3", "hash": "24d42997e1a5c97326b4c87a4e571315fc179a039c294392bf1f0954694edcd0", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_396.txt"}
{"question": "Construct a point Y. Place point H so that it is 1.6 units away from point Y in any direction. Construct a regular polygon with 5 sides starting from points Y and H, call the new vertices ['G', 'V', 'B'], and label the resulting polygon as R. Construct a regular polygon with 9 sides starting from points G and H, call the new vertices ['V6', 'S6', 'U2', 'I2', 'T1', 'M6', 'C9'], and label the resulting polygon as F. Calculate the power V4 of the length of segment segment M6C9 to the exponent 8. Compute the value of V4.", "answer": "42.9497", "hash": "9ae54436a3fb8934d41cfd86d4d058c3130ef26d3251d033cd57eee9aedb72cf", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_371.txt"}
{"question": "Create a point V. Create a point S at a distance of V from point 5. Construct a regular polygon with 8 sides starting from points S and V, call the new vertices ['I', 'C', 'E', 'Q', 'Z', 'A'], and label the resulting polygon as M. Form segment L joining points Q and E. What is the length of segment QE?", "answer": "5.0", "hash": "a7d683e60e220ac84989b3f7a80d66a0a23d0cf70c9907afff3f8be757af6041", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_875.txt"}
{"question": "Create a point I. Construct a point Y. Construct a regular polygon with 4 sides starting from points I and Y, call the new vertices ['F', 'U'], and label the resulting polygon as M. Measure the angle A formed by points F, U, and I. What is the measure of angle FUI?", "answer": "4.7124", "hash": "b9633643834f3494a74c7fce13bc909a824617ee7ee6a01ae547e0985d15237a", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_994.txt"}
{"question": "Create a point P. Create point Y such that it lies 4.7 units from point P in any direction. Reflect point Y across point P, and call the resulting point O. Determine point V by reflecting point P through point O. Create a regular 9-sided polygon beginning at points O and V, name the additional vertices ['F7', 'Y3', 'P2', 'F5', 'G8', 'B3', 'U1'], and denote the polygon as X. What is the area of polygon X?", "answer": "136.5565", "hash": "75ba1109c1e69354a80a5886db00f5bf90d82ac40e9c0fb0630c9f94bd44e031", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_800.txt"}
{"question": "Position a point B. Place a point E that is B units away from point 3. Construct a regular polygon with 6 sides starting from points E and B, call the new vertices ['W', 'J', 'H', 'O'], and label the resulting polygon as C. Identify the point F at the middle of segment segment JH. Create a regular 8-sided polygon beginning at points W and F, name the additional vertices ['P4', 'T7', 'H3', 'I2', 'Q3', 'Y8'], and denote the polygon as K4. Determine the area Z6 of polygon K4. Compute the value of Z6.", "answer": "76.0477", "hash": "2d44fe052eaf2702a42d1bb1050214bcc8b28c29c54c726c6827d0ef34a77bb9", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_820.txt"}
{"question": "Place a point T. Construct a point P at distance T from point 7. Form a circle H centered at point P such that point T lies on it. Find the radius F of circle H. Calculate the value of F.", "answer": "7.0", "hash": "ffd508e20da56b18da48597a783440e031570a5bffde0ecea98c710c42716bff", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_787.txt"}
{"question": "Calculate the sum N of measures 4.1 and 2.5. Calculate the value of N.", "answer": "6.6", "hash": "bc7f675d10e76cf1d6e34fad57e9a402f0886d2eb418384025d6ba20091a511a", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_330.txt"}
{"question": "Compute D as the difference between measures 1.1 and 3.7. Compute the value of D.", "answer": "-2.6", "hash": "788d9cae2d06d348421818098782bf3b78850d53f4ae23a4a6de641fa3b835fb", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_535.txt"}
{"question": "Construct a point L. Construct a point I at distance L from point 5. Form the perpendicular bisector P of the segment from point L to point I. Create ray D originating from point L and extending through point I. Determine the point K that is equidistant from points I and L. Reflect point I across line P, and call the resulting point F. Construct the angle bisector M of angle LKF. Construct a line Y through point L parallel to ray D. Reflect point L across line M, and call the resulting point C. Create point S as the reflection of point K across line Y. Find the length U between points S and C. Compute the value of U.", "answer": "2.5", "hash": "349781bdc9d99200cbbb72b9708c216bcdb750be92366185a998a8855fcd90cd", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_593.txt"}
{"question": "Create a point O. Create point L such that it lies 4.8 units from point O in any direction. Establish a line segment R from point O to point L. Identify the point X at the middle of segment segment OL. Reflect point L across point X, and call the resulting point J. Form segment K4 joining points J and X. Find the length of segment JX.", "answer": "2.4", "hash": "e53f439adc93838a8167816a143641f12ba6a1a096c5bfa4b1226eb388f87e28", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_12.txt"}
{"question": "Mark a point N. Place point L so that it is 2.6 units away from point N in any direction. Find the midpoint O of points L and N. Construct segment M from point O to point N. Find the length of segment ON.", "answer": "1.3", "hash": "8614ae8b364f0aba06e478b9bb7f29bb1c7ffd44e3aec42bf89073f35878e562", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_856.txt"}
{"question": "Position a point Q. Mark a point J such that its distance from point 3 is Q. Place a point K. Measure the distance M between points K and J. Measure the distance C between points J and K. Compute X as the ratio of measure M to measure C. Compute the value of X.", "answer": "1.0", "hash": "f18b23c44b41f0d82f3a3b45dc9083d4eadc0384fe321af00c795aa50b0a2de3", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_411.txt"}
{"question": "Create a point Z. Place point P so that it is 2.4 units away from point Z in any direction. Create a regular 6-sided polygon beginning at points P and Z, name the additional vertices ['C', 'S', 'L', 'G'], and denote the polygon as M. Form segment Y9 joining points C and P. Find the length of segment CP.", "answer": "4.1569", "hash": "84cb574235c5f41225ed58e067d8fbd0a0be7740e39d2f05d8474c1d4e5e2aab", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_272.txt"}
{"question": "Mark a point M. Mark point A at a distance of 4.3 from point M in an arbitrary direction. Construct a regular polygon with 9 sides starting from points M and A, call the new vertices ['L', 'N', 'F', 'E', 'T', 'C', 'V'], and label the resulting polygon as B. Mark the point I2 where segments segment LN and segment NF meet. Create a line segment W2 between points I2 and A. Find the length of segment I2A.", "answer": "8.0814", "hash": "2c175ffc10193d96321a96003c77567fffd22799283d4fd15c56f37de5bc4f34", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_550.txt"}
{"question": "Create a point X. Position point S at a distance of 4.9 from point X, in whichever direction you choose. Construct a regular polygon with 7 sides starting from points X and S, call the new vertices ['R', 'D', 'I', 'U', 'M'], and label the resulting polygon as L. Find the measure of angle B4 formed by points D, U, and R. Find the measure of angle DUR.", "answer": "5.8344", "hash": "83192e474d34b55a5e63abdac11ead5a0de261eb9bac0f2609d6afd5817ee03d", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_830.txt"}
{"question": "Position a point D. Place point G so that it is 4.5 units away from point D in any direction. Reflect point D across point G, and call the resulting point H. Find the midpoint S of points H and G. Construct a regular polygon with 7 sides starting from points H and S, call the new vertices ['L5', 'P2', 'G9', 'S4', 'G7'], and label the resulting polygon as H8. What is the area of polygon H8?", "answer": "18.3967", "hash": "a3ca8b648c230ca3eaeab4e86a6a8225cde2759a4f74cfa29519a084a9340ceb", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_997.txt"}
{"question": "Position a point A. Position point H at a distance of 1.2 from point A, in whichever direction you choose. Construct a regular polygon with 7 sides starting from points A and H, call the new vertices ['D', 'N', 'Q', 'B', 'M'], and label the resulting polygon as L. Establish the lines C, O that divide the angles between segments segment NQ and segment DN into equal parts. Find point N8 such that line C is the perpendicular bisector of segment from D to N8. Calculate the difference R5 between measures 1.7 and 1.0. Construct point H7 on line C, at distance 2.2 from point H. Find the length Y1 between points H7 and N8. Compute A5 as the ratio of measure Y1 to measure R5. Calculate the value of A5.", "answer": "2.8598", "hash": "7e03fec4c8504fd0ea3c8bc8e19c5edcc4024c04083464cbd5df0e6dfe393720", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_924.txt"}
{"question": "Mark a point Z. Construct point G at distance 4.8 from point Z in a random direction. Place point A so that it is 4.5 units away from point G in any direction. Construct the angle bisector X of angle AGZ. Construct a line S through points G and Z. Mark the point Y where lines S and X meet. Mark point O on line S at a distance of 3.7 from point Y. Form segment N joining points Y and O. Find the length of segment YO.", "answer": "3.7", "hash": "172bbf1faa789fe4302edc46c02a4fc4671e2b2b73743322c98574a73122ffb2", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_608.txt"}
{"question": "Create a point Y. Mark point T at a distance of 2.7 from point Y in an arbitrary direction. Position a point X so that it is exactly T units from point 2. Draw a circle N centered at T that passes through point X. Measure the radius E of circle N. Compute the value of E.", "answer": "2.0", "hash": "597cbc61fc1152616fd32967428e0a94be0d191296110db514eb463ed8bf2102", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_518.txt"}
{"question": "Place a point G. Mark a point I such that its distance from point 7 is G. Construct the perpendicular bisector C of points G and I. Determine point Z by reflecting point I over line C. Determine point P by reflecting point G through point I. Create a circle U with its center at G and containing point Z on its circumference. Draw the perpendicular bisector K of the line segment connecting points P and I. Create point X on line K so that its distance from point Z is 1.1. Construct a point A on circle U. Compute the length Y of the straight line from point A to point X. Compute the value of Y.", "answer": "10.5575", "hash": "da9cb989d5e694e3a83fcf379f0dbbf2f3941bdcdc068ce6dd8b4b4b28a8d808", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_249.txt"}
{"question": "Create a point Y. Construct a point P at distance Y from point 5. Create ray K originating from point Y and extending through point P. Create point A as the reflection of point Y across point P. Draw a line J passing through point Y that is parallel to ray K. Create a line M through point P that forms a right angle with ray K. Establish a line U through point Y that runs parallel to line M. Mark the point F where lines U and J meet. Construct a regular polygon with 3 sides starting from points F and A, call the new vertices ['H'], and label the resulting polygon as I. Create a line segment T3 between points A and H. Find the length of segment AH.", "answer": "10.0", "hash": "da380768cc0c22823f94e277343aa6f0cb4502861c2dfe3856c4300c7beab66a", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_141.txt"}
{"question": "Construct a point L. Create point F such that it lies 4.9 units from point L in any direction. Create point X such that it lies 3.9 units from point F in any direction. Create a line segment G between points X and F. Compute D as the length of segment segment XF raised to the power of 8. Compute the value of D.", "answer": "53520.0926", "hash": "8ec10fc4463439c45139b518ef4ac4076d1cee3ab0259d69e851e8cf45a599a2", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_394.txt"}
{"question": "Construct a point J. Create a point N. Construct a regular polygon with 5 sides starting from points N and J, call the new vertices ['Q', 'K', 'M'], and label the resulting polygon as Z. Form the perpendicular bisector E of the segment from point Q to point K. Create a regular 8-sided polygon beginning at points N and K, name the additional vertices ['O', 'V', 'N7', 'K6', 'N4', 'C7'], and denote the polygon as C. Reflect point K6 across line E, and call the resulting point D7. Measure the angle N8 formed by points N7, M, and D7. Find the measure of angle N7MD7.", "answer": "2.6889", "hash": "f16ff1cf8092d8e7e6852224f78f49a839f3104e66c18a8fe483d6327e135c2e", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_906.txt"}
{"question": "Position a point H. Mark a point U such that its distance from point 3 is H. Determine point J by reflecting point H through point U. Determine point S by reflecting point U through point H. Find the midpoint I of points J and H. Construct a regular polygon with 3 sides starting from points S and I, call the new vertices ['V'], and label the resulting polygon as A. Compute Y2 as the length of segment segment SI raised to the power of 5. Calculate the value of Y2.", "answer": "7776.0", "hash": "343097b7d02d3aa4ec2e82e33f94ef482be104194a89fc4ead574571f60bfb87", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_78.txt"}
{"question": "Mark a point L. Position a point A so that it is exactly L units from point 6. Construct point J as the image of point A when reflected over point L. Find the midpoint K of points L and J. Create a circle F with its center at A and containing point L on its circumference. Identify point O as the center point of circle F. Create a regular 6-sided polygon beginning at points O and K, name the additional vertices ['Y', 'J1', 'G6', 'Y6'], and denote the polygon as B. What is the area of polygon B?", "answer": "210.4442", "hash": "d7feb2b590bcbbbf3e6e2fef768f060800e959f19567e3eb0d70e16df4457bd7", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_126.txt"}
{"question": "Create a point A. Place point K so that it is 3.3 units away from point A in any direction. Find the midpoint B of points A and K. Create a regular 9-sided polygon beginning at points B and K, name the additional vertices ['I', 'T', 'W', 'D', 'G', 'N', 'J'], and denote the polygon as Z. Determine the distance V3 from point K to point D. Calculate the value of V3.", "answer": "4.751", "hash": "93ae9c4125df07e5105a09e6f570f413a243e593066e6bd0b4e59f2236d74ec4", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_676.txt"}
{"question": "Place a point Q. Place point R so that it is 5.0 units away from point Q in any direction. Create a regular 3-sided polygon beginning at points Q and R, name the additional vertices ['M'], and denote the polygon as X. Create a regular 3-sided polygon beginning at points M and R, name the additional vertices ['J'], and denote the polygon as O. What is the area of polygon O?", "answer": "10.8253", "hash": "08b196075498c41570ba6f0e551b099c3032f839dd666d8a8ee8a2a26b7868ff", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_651.txt"}
{"question": "Mark a point I. Place point K so that it is 2.7 units away from point I in any direction. Find point N such that point I is the midpoint of the segment from K to N. Construct a regular polygon with 8 sides starting from points K and I, call the new vertices ['S', 'F', 'O', 'V', 'P', 'X1'], and label the resulting polygon as R. Create a regular 7-sided polygon beginning at points P and N, name the additional vertices ['E8', 'V6', 'I1', 'W1', 'O1'], and denote the polygon as C5. Draw a line segment F4 connecting points X1 and W1. Find the length of segment X1W1.", "answer": "18.1399", "hash": "2353666edf581fddf5c7059c85dbd00c4e473dc06c09114cfda722fb40262de3", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_289.txt"}
{"question": "Position a point W. Mark a point U such that its distance from point 2 is W. Construct a line M through points U and W. Establish a line F through point W that runs parallel to line M. Draw a circle Z centered at W that passes through point U. Locate the midpoint P between points U and W. Construct a point O on circle Z. Construct a regular polygon with 2 sides starting from points U and O, call the new vertices [], and label the resulting polygon as B. Mark the point T where segment segment OU meets line F. Determine the distance B6 from point P to point T. Compute the value of B6.", "answer": "1.0", "hash": "0dc84aa383e4205502a786a4a6a1331cca7d8f6438e68617a331ba0baa382831", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_14.txt"}
{"question": "Position a point A. Position a point Z. Draw the perpendicular bisector K of the line segment connecting points Z and A. Mark a point R that lies on line K. Place point H so that it is 3.8 units away from point R in any direction. Create point Q such that it lies 2.3 units from point H in any direction. Compute the length P of the straight line from point Q to point H. Compute the value of P.", "answer": "2.3", "hash": "b6e9f2688fcf0375d28f35b6fbae3399c685e5e3ebf333d2b11152a8fd29d468", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_201.txt"}
{"question": "Construct a point H. Position a point L so that it is exactly H units from point 7. Create a regular 2-sided polygon beginning at points L and H, name the additional vertices [], and denote the polygon as R. Identify the point Q at the middle of segment segment HL. Construct a circle T with center Q passing through point H. Determine the radius B of circle T. Compute the value of B.", "answer": "3.5", "hash": "6f10c268f4239d16080bbb165f3463131d4236a09ce87e50b6def4e566dc1c66", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_412.txt"}
{"question": "Create a point B. Position point O at a distance of 2.3 from point B, in whichever direction you choose. Create vector D directed from point O to point B. Construct point S by shifting point O in the direction and magnitude of vector D. Construct point T as the image of point O when reflected over point S. Construct a regular polygon with 8 sides starting from points T and O, call the new vertices ['P8', 'S8', 'Y7', 'P1', 'X2', 'D1'], and label the resulting polygon as H3. What is the area of polygon H3?", "answer": "102.1695", "hash": "b7ff713eb2833f4ee7cba4089151ac524b6e625dae47545c6ed6f9d51b7cad38", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_741.txt"}
{"question": "Create a point Z. Construct a point W at distance Z from point 1. Form segment V joining points Z and W. Establish a line F through point Z that is parallel to segment segment ZW. Construct a line B through point Z parallel to segment segment ZW. Position a point M so that it is exactly W units from point 7. Establish a circle Y with center M and radius equal to the distance from M to Z. Find the intersection points K and R of line B and circle Y. Determine point D as the result of inverting point R with respect to circle Y. Place point H on line F such that it is 1.6 units away from point D. Form segment B7 joining points R and H. What is the length of segment RH?", "answer": "1.6", "hash": "44e37bf90d8226b72e93cb2225e060d1ed610fc37457f1304ae588dd324e94a9", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_887.txt"}
{"question": "Compute W as the difference between measures 4.1 and 3.1. Compute the value of W.", "answer": "1.0", "hash": "f25c89dbbccac1e1bff974ef5c3fc5a99a1045963c0da1c4195e2bece95c019e", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_447.txt"}
{"question": "Construct a point U. Mark a point V such that its distance from point 8 is U. Construct a circle D with center U passing through point V. Identify point C as the center point of circle D. Compute the length Q of the straight line from point C to point V. Calculate the value of Q.", "answer": "8.0", "hash": "646cec5d694cbbbf277ab06edf7df9b99d98b2c6eaece2d1a0e5437260d9a3f8", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_52.txt"}
{"question": "Create a point S. Position point Z at a distance of 4.0 from point S, in whichever direction you choose. Create a line segment K between points Z and S. Establish the line F that divides the segment between Z and S into two equal parts and is perpendicular to it. Create point N on line F so that its distance from point S is 1.6. Form a circle R centered at point Z such that point S lies on it. Construct line Q as the image of line F when reflected over point N. Determine the point C where segment segment ZS intersects line Q. Identify the points V and D common to both line F and circle R. Construct segment U from point V to point D. Determine the point I8 where segments segment ZS and segment VD intersect. Create a regular 9-sided polygon beginning at points V and I8, name the additional vertices ['B3', 'G6', 'E7', 'R6', 'S1', 'D9', 'Y3'], and denote the polygon as A3. Calculate the measure of angle T5 with vertex at C and sides passing through G6 and B3. What is the measure of angle G6CB3?", "answer": "5.9341", "hash": "836acedc4c2afcaea65e85d17f47bdf56a5e55eff05e77247063a411a6884790", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_582.txt"}
{"question": "Position a point Y. Place point N so that it is 4.9 units away from point Y in any direction. Construct point L as the image of point N when reflected over point Y. Construct ray P starting at point N and passing through point L. Form a line R through point N that is at a 90-degree angle to ray P. Determine the point Z that is equidistant from points L and N. Construct point S on line R, at distance 2.8 from point Z. Determine the point I that is equidistant from points Z and Y. Determine point H by reflecting point S through point I. Draw a line segment Q connecting points Z and H. Find the length of segment ZH.", "answer": "5.6436", "hash": "971bad51b431269ba18511831ee29a547a5a30377bdb07690f047467236536dc", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_454.txt"}
{"question": "Place a point G. Mark a point R such that its distance from point 10 is G. Construct point P as the image of point R when reflected over point G. Construct a regular polygon with 7 sides starting from points P and G, call the new vertices ['K', 'Q', 'M', 'V', 'E'], and label the resulting polygon as S. Measure the angle T formed by points K, Q, and E. Find the measure of angle KQE.", "answer": "4.9368", "hash": "d9036202e22414d6f9de2cbd7a0dc10ec0c723c3c4c9d092a6f8f74ae4a311db", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_526.txt"}
{"question": "Position a point R. Construct a point V at distance R from point 9. Position point M at a distance of 1.7 from point R, in whichever direction you choose. Construct a regular polygon with 6 sides starting from points V and M, call the new vertices ['A5', 'Z8', 'F4', 'D4'], and label the resulting polygon as J. Calculate the measure of angle S7 with vertex at F4 and sides passing through Z8 and D4. What is the measure of angle Z8F4D4?", "answer": "4.1888", "hash": "fbfe89a9b20d4abf0f306603aa275de90450aa6ae0ce11099d7ccfc83cd8c364", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_261.txt"}
{"question": "Construct a point E. Place a point F. Mark a point Q such that its distance from point 10 is F. Define vector V starting at point F and ending at point E. Determine point M as the image of point Q when translated by vector V. Establish the ray O that divides angle FMQ into two congruent angles. Create a line G connecting points Q and M. Construct a regular polygon with 6 sides starting from points E and M, call the new vertices ['U', 'Y', 'N', 'T'], and label the resulting polygon as X. Identify the point L common to both lines O and G. Create point O9 as the reflection of point L across segment segment YN. Form segment T5 joining points N and O9. What is the length of segment NO9?", "answer": "20.0", "hash": "7f3af09b5fc2378b12cceecb0fed1783eed4d3caf8949cf38148f8ccf1ce628f", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_666.txt"}
{"question": "Construct a point B. Place a point G that is B units away from point 6. Create a regular 7-sided polygon beginning at points G and B, name the additional vertices ['X', 'Y', 'T', 'S', 'L'], and denote the polygon as O. Identify the midpoint F of the segment connecting points G and Y. Draw a line segment N connecting points F and S. What is the length of segment FS?", "answer": "8.4529", "hash": "a04ef1fba8dab0e6b199c1ec9660518d59c9ec4db869a0a96a1180c10c5e06be", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_117.txt"}
{"question": "Position a point D. Construct point G at distance 3.0 from point D in a random direction. Establish a line segment Z from point D to point G. What is the length of segment DG?", "answer": "3.0", "hash": "272ca5418e1ac96b6ed341d0ad666de655861ea9d2283663888aca75438fa15d", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_833.txt"}
{"question": "Mark a point H. Create point N such that it lies 1.3 units from point H in any direction. Form a line A that goes through points H and N. Construct a point Q at distance N from point 3. Create point R as the reflection of point N across line A. Establish a line segment Y from point Q to point R. Find the length of segment QR.", "answer": "3.0", "hash": "d070a5a0a22c0675d272330e62187eaaf0ef0c35e9b7b8fc2e3b898046eed6fe", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_356.txt"}
{"question": "Place a point F. Position a point K so that it is exactly F units from point 6. Create point T as the reflection of point F across point K. Position a point Q so that it is exactly T units from point 9. Establish a line segment S3 from point T to point Q. Find the length of segment TQ.", "answer": "9.0", "hash": "abe51fccc3800efb8d040979a0070b16dabf9deb2b65e9b6207533954137795d", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_341.txt"}
{"question": "Construct a point F. Mark a point S. Construct the perpendicular bisector Z of points S and F. Draw ray U with endpoint at F that passes through point S. Find the intersection point Y of ray U and line Z. Create a regular 4-sided polygon beginning at points F and Y, name the additional vertices ['R', 'E'], and denote the polygon as O. Create point C as the reflection of point F across segment segment EF. Measure the angle E2 formed by points R, C, and S. Find the measure of angle RCS.", "answer": "5.4978", "hash": "4f7f21ec008fa7456832961a97b28cc35a3f1e4071d4f35f90441e0042a36761", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_747.txt"}
{"question": "Create a point T. Place a point X. Create a regular 10-sided polygon beginning at points X and T, name the additional vertices ['W', 'Z', 'L', 'I', 'Y', 'E', 'J', 'P8'], and denote the polygon as B. Construct a regular polygon with 6 sides starting from points P8 and Z, call the new vertices ['T2', 'Z7', 'A4', 'O2'], and label the resulting polygon as O9. Locate the midpoint R3 of segment segment A4O2. Find the measure of angle X4 formed by points R3, T, and Y. What is the measure of angle R3TY?", "answer": "5.8594", "hash": "1b8b04bcb662496b0f8591e707c472fec9536ef2548f1e6e803b771c678305cc", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_150.txt"}
{"question": "Mark a point W. Place a point P that is W units away from point 1. Construct a regular polygon with 3 sides starting from points W and P, call the new vertices ['S'], and label the resulting polygon as O. Compute M as the length of segment segment SW raised to the power of 3. Compute the value of M.", "answer": "1.0", "hash": "29c41fb59427d978a0cb43844abbcc248b361519cce6214d0189baf545a4e718", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_677.txt"}
{"question": "Position a point V. Create a point X. Establish a line segment M from point X to point V. Calculate the power C of the length of segment segment XV to the exponent 3. Calculate the power R of the length of segment segment XV to the exponent 3. Compute I as the ratio of measure R to measure C. Compute the value of I.", "answer": "1.0", "hash": "1ea82f4b81d7fb93900909562666f92ef36f82b1f4ee34b51988760181b1cb97", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_884.txt"}
{"question": "Construct a point C. Place a point Y that is C units away from point 10. Construct a regular polygon with 5 sides starting from points C and Y, call the new vertices ['F', 'H', 'O'], and label the resulting polygon as M. Create a line X connecting points C and Y. Locate the point I at which segments segment FH and segment HO cross each other. Create a regular 5-sided polygon beginning at points F and I, name the additional vertices ['R6', 'S5', 'X9'], and denote the polygon as Z8. Establish a circle M3 that passes through each of the points F, O, and I. Find the intersection points X7 and T3 of circle circle FOI and line X. Measure the distance M4 between points S5 and X7. Calculate the value of M4.", "answer": "10.0", "hash": "3932e7a98f703e6e6ee9f0b4d7a6b43250175b74562d33b341045c723e47a348", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_235.txt"}
{"question": "Place a point F. Create point C such that it lies 4.6 units from point F in any direction. Form a line I that goes through points F and C. Create point N on line I so that its distance from point F is 2.7. Construct a regular polygon with 8 sides starting from points N and C, call the new vertices ['K', 'U', 'X', 'W', 'A', 'T'], and label the resulting polygon as G. Compute the angle R formed by the rays from point X to points T and C. Find the measure of angle TXC.", "answer": "0.7854", "hash": "7761fb3b3eaa6a7402e1d42bb9b3a2902691107416f714ab40f2d1eb1c80c367", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_19.txt"}
{"question": "Construct a point I. Position point C at a distance of 4.3 from point I, in whichever direction you choose. Measure the distance P between points C and I. Compute the value of P.", "answer": "4.3", "hash": "0ad78a8ced9ee90345fc66fc4e3bdc6b3f7403db26682de4f37ad5cabfdf436b", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_946.txt"}
{"question": "Position a point C. Mark point O at a distance of 1.3 from point C in an arbitrary direction. Create the line S that perpendicularly bisects the segment between points C and O. Construct segment P from point O to point C. Establish a circle N with center point C and radius identical to the length of segment segment OC. Locate the points K and W at which line S crosses circle N. Create a regular 3-sided polygon beginning at points K and C, name the additional vertices ['I'], and denote the polygon as H. Determine the point T where segments segment IK and segment KC intersect. Find the length X9 between points W and T. Calculate the value of X9.", "answer": "2.2517", "hash": "86acb94751927d9941aaaee62541f98a9366223608516a65660bfcec9f0681e4", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_687.txt"}
{"question": "Position a point R. Place a point Z. Construct a regular polygon with 9 sides starting from points R and Z, call the new vertices ['U', 'E', 'W', 'C', 'Y', 'D', 'J'], and label the resulting polygon as G. Create a circle F containing points C, Z, and E on its circumference. Find the intersection points R5 and B6 of circle circle CZE and segment segment ZU. Find the measure of angle V2 formed by points U, E, and B6. Find the measure of angle UEB6.", "answer": "5.9341", "hash": "3d72790e5e0f1783f623f8a51e050da894578c5c5caed844e8803af064ccef25", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_812.txt"}
{"question": "Position a point Y. Create point F such that it lies 2.4 units from point Y in any direction. Create a regular 7-sided polygon beginning at points F and Y, name the additional vertices ['L', 'K', 'U', 'P', 'C'], and denote the polygon as V. Find the area K3 enclosed by polygon V. Calculate the value of K3.", "answer": "20.9313", "hash": "a4e9fa35628b9e6a84040118cdabb18152fe149d2f38aafeb3c04d86a6bf2d36", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_480.txt"}
{"question": "Position a point Y. Construct a point A at distance Y from point 10. Construct a regular polygon with 3 sides starting from points A and Y, call the new vertices ['O'], and label the resulting polygon as R. Construct point P as the image of point O when reflected over point A. Create a regular 8-sided polygon beginning at points O and P, name the additional vertices ['M4', 'G8', 'J2', 'I3', 'D7', 'M9'], and denote the polygon as U. What is the area of polygon U?", "answer": "1931.3708", "hash": "4277e3160b527080dd2656d79c05f2775e2270a5e4a6f10942c37725d76675eb", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_922.txt"}
{"question": "Create a point L. Create a point N at a distance of L from point 4. Construct point J as the image of point N when reflected over point L. Construct point O as the image of point J when reflected over point L. Construct a regular polygon with 4 sides starting from points O and J, call the new vertices ['S', 'Q'], and label the resulting polygon as F. Locate the midpoint P between points O and J. Draw a line segment X3 connecting points Q and P. What is the length of segment QP?", "answer": "8.9443", "hash": "ad19826e4dd0b9151393f8c9307abd163751fd1577ad4b79049e7e270a92efbb", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_198.txt"}
{"question": "Construct a point P. Calculate the difference I between measures 1.3 and 3.7. Construct a point J at distance P from point 1. Measure the distance U between points P and J. Calculate the ratio K of measure I to measure U. Compute the value of K.", "answer": "-2.4", "hash": "7506019df66b1a014ec293ad2f777e9ab21c916a9bba082f9f85b65afba490ee", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_892.txt"}
{"question": "Position a point R. Place point N so that it is 1.2 units away from point R in any direction. Establish a circle Z with center N and radius equal to the distance from N to R. Construct the polar line H of point R with respect to circle Z. Mark the point A where line H meets circle Z. Construct segment F5 from point N to point A. What is the length of segment NA?", "answer": "1.2", "hash": "3c191c34b0865a8755e1e5f5e1d8f8c90d7b297ed03f293499f2d732570e836c", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_463.txt"}
{"question": "Position a point E. Create point A such that it lies 2.4 units from point E in any direction. Position a point S so that it is exactly E units from point 8. Draw a circle Y that passes through the three points S, E, and A. Construct circle U as the image of circle circle SEA when reflected over point E. Create a line I connecting points A and E. Define point G to be the center of circle U. Mark point O on line I at a distance of 1.1 from point G. Measure the distance W between points O and E. Compute the value of W.", "answer": "2.3", "hash": "099008298a247a09e71b26f66deb4c750c02ca6140025de5e29639573f84f4a3", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_496.txt"}
{"question": "Place a point B. Construct a point R at distance B from point 1. Draw a line G that passes through points B and R. Construct a circle S with center R passing through point B. Identify the points I and L common to both line G and circle S. Determine the distance O from point R to point L. Calculate the value of O.", "answer": "1.0", "hash": "75d3b3f2fe84899cd3f85cb9cfd9fe3208f6034baceabd84d113ab86475f680a", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_803.txt"}
{"question": "Mark a point Q. Place a point K that is Q units away from point 3. Create a circle J with its center at K and containing point Q on its circumference. Define point M to be the center of circle J. Mark a point Z on the circumference of circle J. Construct segment G from point M to point Z. What is the length of segment MZ?", "answer": "3.0", "hash": "1c5eb389538ff26a25e6b31d471f87dc46534ce454881e3166eb37e96e9934bc", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_995.txt"}
{"question": "Create a point W. Position a point G so that it is exactly W units from point 7. Identify the midpoint X of the segment connecting points G and W. Construct a regular polygon with 7 sides starting from points W and X, call the new vertices ['K', 'B', 'A', 'I', 'M'], and label the resulting polygon as O. What is the area of polygon O?", "answer": "44.5154", "hash": "ec76a82228a1009af6b16c2279b1d6bab7883c7b2f1f76b3f03e4fe360e2b5b6", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_140.txt"}
{"question": "Position a point G. Mark a point H such that its distance from point 1 is G. Create a regular 2-sided polygon beginning at points H and G, name the additional vertices [], and denote the polygon as E. Locate the midpoint B between points G and H. Locate the midpoint K between points H and B. Determine the point Y that divides segment segment GH into two equal parts. Form segment R joining points Y and K. Calculate the power S of the length of segment segment YK to the exponent 2. Compute the value of S.", "answer": "0.0625", "hash": "f7351371ec75b486bb3bdfeca4b6b2f76244689d684e0a0c53bb10480a7cb1c0", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_999.txt"}
{"question": "Position a point L. Construct a point A at distance L from point 3. Create a regular 5-sided polygon beginning at points L and A, name the additional vertices ['S', 'D', 'B'], and denote the polygon as G. Measure the distance M between points S and A. Calculate the value of M.", "answer": "3.0", "hash": "90bbe51f8d90508fbdeaa1c9e3feeedb2855a9a4bd0eda70610d99bf926b9fde", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_44.txt"}
{"question": "Mark a point N. Position a point U so that it is exactly N units from point 9. Form segment E joining points N and U. Reflect point N across segment segment NU, and call the resulting point F. Establish a line segment M from point F to point U. What is the length of segment FU?", "answer": "9.0", "hash": "c984a2fdcf7eee3d36a6f9f636457770863cf3c82bb6ad163ba41f939606af3d", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_118.txt"}
{"question": "Create a point H. Position a point Z so that it is exactly H units from point 2. Construct a regular polygon with 9 sides starting from points Z and H, call the new vertices ['K', 'S', 'R', 'U', 'O', 'F', 'N'], and label the resulting polygon as T. Construct a point P at distance H from point 6. Determine point J5 by reflecting point K through point F. Create a regular 10-sided polygon beginning at points J5 and P, name the additional vertices ['K1', 'A1', 'T9', 'U6', 'B2', 'Z5', 'W1', 'S7'], and denote the polygon as G6. Find the measure of angle L5 formed by points Z5, S7, and K1. Find the measure of angle Z5S7K1.", "answer": "4.7124", "hash": "bf3c1d51463919c460cc2525c4ce2543047c2b4409ea8f388f4b2b290c329ac3", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_444.txt"}
{"question": "Mark a point B. Mark a point U such that its distance from point 1 is B. Create a regular 2-sided polygon beginning at points B and U, name the additional vertices [], and denote the polygon as M. Compute E as the length of segment segment BU raised to the power of 5. Compute the value of E.", "answer": "1.0", "hash": "b0e3c9b1c1fe89a49beba1d59d17c6eed2569e56bfb8f231d1dab79662da8685", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_705.txt"}
{"question": "Create a point P. Place a point I that is P units away from point 7. Form a line F that goes through points I and P. Draw a line L passing through point I that is perpendicular to line F. Construct a circle R with center P passing through point I. Establish a line W passing through both points I and P. Mark the point C where line L meets circle R. Mark the points H and M where circle R meets line W. Create a line segment A4 between points C and H. Find the length of segment CH.", "answer": "14.0", "hash": "e56ebf4a9e46c7b545edd512ffee3359e07967b79ff72ef425141196bfed2d41", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_670.txt"}
{"question": "Mark a point O. Create point C such that it lies 3.4 units from point O in any direction. Construct a regular polygon with 4 sides starting from points O and C, call the new vertices ['S', 'Q'], and label the resulting polygon as U. Establish the ray E that divides angle COQ into two congruent angles. Determine point T by reflecting point C over line E. Create a line segment R between points T and S. Find the length of segment TS.", "answer": "3.4", "hash": "5ed2e9046bdcbc2f870541cb0338a579bbddbc5e6ee18b6aeca2a242e11548c8", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_503.txt"}
{"question": "Mark a point R. Create a point D at a distance of R from point 7. Draw a circle K centered at R that passes through point D. Identify the midpoint L of the segment connecting points R and D. Construct point O as the image of point L under inversion in circle K. Determine the angle J created by the three points O, D, and L. Find the measure of angle ODL.", "answer": "3.1416", "hash": "598bec56c82c1ee87ba6e9d9436190f7aba81605fa102d8c79e416fb5ca2143a", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_767.txt"}
{"question": "Construct a point U. Construct point D at distance 2.6 from point U in a random direction. Draw a line segment Z connecting points D and U. Calculate the power O6 of the length of segment segment DU to the exponent 5. Compute the value of O6.", "answer": "118.8138", "hash": "0c993119c6b6db289fa0e40f56b2bb4f139222178eae609ccf8ccab09718f8e3", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_609.txt"}
{"question": "Place a point R. Create a point F at a distance of R from point 1. Determine point V by reflecting point F through point R. Construct a circle Q with center V passing through point R. Find circle D by reflecting circle Q through point V. Draw the angle bisector E that divides angle RVF into two equal parts. Identify the points N and J common to both circle D and line E. Construct segment C from point F to point N. What is the length of segment FN?", "answer": "1.0", "hash": "1d20866b5a14aabddc9c7225372fee985ed16c77342f96fe5783072b1c6b4fb0", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_655.txt"}
{"question": "Create a point I. Create a point A at a distance of I from point 2. Position point Y at a distance of 2.3 from point A, in whichever direction you choose. Draw a line segment D connecting points Y and A. Find the length of segment YA.", "answer": "2.3", "hash": "a4c5ed59ea772c6c9b516accdb1ff39a2685564a8614fa95d20a205f8fa83699", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_644.txt"}
{"question": "Position a point O. Place a point G that is O units away from point 10. Construct a regular polygon with 10 sides starting from points G and O, call the new vertices ['T', 'K', 'D', 'A', 'Y', 'U', 'W', 'S'], and label the resulting polygon as V. Determine the point L that is equidistant from points D and G. Create point M4 as the reflection of point O across segment segment SG. Establish a line segment D8 from point M4 to point L. Find the length of segment M4L.", "answer": "22.7531", "hash": "6e7ac40b4646aff8921d1d14b1512cf27c0c94fb174818b7b9e4a6472a1f02b0", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_919.txt"}
{"question": "Construct a point M. Construct a point L at distance M from point 6. Form vector P with initial point L and terminal point M. Determine point V as the image of point L when translated by vector P. Locate the midpoint B between points V and M. Locate the midpoint Y between points L and B. Find the length D between points Y and V. Calculate the value of D.", "answer": "3.0", "hash": "78095017d3c16ab6dee5d90f7000c381676d9a2ae33fd9135d1540390cec060a", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_17.txt"}
{"question": "Construct a point U. Construct point C at distance 2.0 from point U in a random direction. Construct a regular polygon with 8 sides starting from points U and C, call the new vertices ['H', 'B', 'O', 'S', 'M', 'A'], and label the resulting polygon as X. Form the perpendicular bisector W that cuts segment segment HB into two equal halves. Find the intersection point P of line W and segment segment MA. Find the length J between points P and S. Compute the value of J.", "answer": "2.7979", "hash": "cc32c90ea5c8cdc574fc46afe32350006bec2fc0f0dae988cee1c2c315525875", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_672.txt"}
{"question": "Create a point W. Place a point X. Reflect point X across point W, and call the resulting point R. Construct a point E at distance R from point 4. Create a regular 6-sided polygon beginning at points R and E, name the additional vertices ['O', 'L', 'H', 'C'], and denote the polygon as Q. Determine the point P that divides segment segment OL into two equal parts. Create a regular 5-sided polygon beginning at points P and H, name the additional vertices ['H5', 'E4', 'O5'], and denote the polygon as L5. Compute O2 as the length of segment segment E4O5 raised to the power of 2. Compute the value of O2.", "answer": "28.0", "hash": "ebe1278aafb920794048e8a435b043954d6c7923258028a84b4061ddf7ec7d94", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_658.txt"}
{"question": "Construct a point J. Mark point D at a distance of 2.8 from point J in an arbitrary direction. Create a regular 10-sided polygon beginning at points D and J, name the additional vertices ['Q', 'M', 'H', 'N', 'S', 'V', 'Z', 'P'], and denote the polygon as F. Draw a line segment E1 connecting points P and D. Find the length of segment PD.", "answer": "2.8", "hash": "ba9754406f3b511f44c499dd5bb57d11653a38aea1f5f8ebe69cc5109ef9cfcb", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_571.txt"}
{"question": "Place a point E. Position a point C so that it is exactly E units from point 2. Construct a point T at distance C from point 5. Determine point I by reflecting point T through point C. Construct point A as the image of point C when reflected over point I. Find the midpoint R of points T and A. Create point O as the reflection of point I across point R. Construct a regular polygon with 5 sides starting from points E and O, call the new vertices ['P', 'N', 'W7'], and label the resulting polygon as X. Find the area of polygon X.", "answer": "6.8819", "hash": "65b4fd25b7568a3239a5094636052fbdfadbd31d487ddced4e4f06234094f782", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_532.txt"}
{"question": "Mark a point R. Mark point W at a distance of 2.7 from point R in an arbitrary direction. Create a regular 10-sided polygon beginning at points R and W, name the additional vertices ['L', 'Y', 'O', 'Q', 'H', 'B', 'F1', 'V4'], and denote the polygon as T. Compute I5 as the length of segment segment RW raised to the power of 4. Compute the value of I5.", "answer": "53.1441", "hash": "5c30c172fbf25d917e86891f3df40159d34c1d069d92061016a8d246381a84c9", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_567.txt"}
{"question": "Position a point C. Construct point J at distance 1.3 from point C in a random direction. Create a circle T with its center at J and containing point C on its circumference. Form the tangent line A from point C to circle T. Construct point U on line A, at distance 1.9 from point C. Compute the length P of the straight line from point U to point J. Calculate the value of P.", "answer": "2.3022", "hash": "75a5397caf01fdb9a80da5cd5c92dc51ea950f60cccff27e92a2b19db26ef3f2", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_735.txt"}
{"question": "Position a point W. Create point M such that it lies 2.5 units from point W in any direction. Find point U such that point W is the midpoint of the segment from M to U. Construct a regular polygon with 6 sides starting from points M and W, call the new vertices ['J', 'I', 'C', 'E9'], and label the resulting polygon as E. Reflect point U across segment segment E9M, and call the resulting point V9. Mark a point A1 that lies on segment segment CE9. Determine the angle B3 created by the three points A1, C, and V9. What is the measure of angle A1CV9?", "answer": "0.2426", "hash": "97d6d19ac6c238fd8e1c0a2d59897cde5eab76fc8c8becb3a02fa4448841024c", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_746.txt"}
{"question": "Construct a point O. Create a point E at a distance of O from point 2. Compute the length G of the straight line from point O to point E. Compute the value of G.", "answer": "2.0", "hash": "76e89e2be8f9587b829d78b57a45d49d264c76db65cec209dbe0b36c73ec38fc", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_379.txt"}
{"question": "Mark a point N. Mark a point Q such that its distance from point 9 is N. Create a regular 1-sided polygon beginning at points N and Q, name the additional vertices ['C'], and denote the polygon as Y. Establish a circle F with center point N and radius identical to the length of segment segment NN. Locate the point G at which circle F crosses segment C. Identify the point M at the middle of segment segment NN. Find the length S between points M and G. Compute the value of S.", "answer": "4.5", "hash": "2fbcbfa731c6583a442f18fbc4af8a8027912a93189f3c1e7a2b008a5afb396c", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_219.txt"}
{"question": "Place a point J. Mark a point X. Find point Y such that point J is the midpoint of the segment from X to Y. Draw the perpendicular bisector N of the line segment connecting points Y and X. Construct segment W from point X to point J. Determine the point A that divides segment segment XJ into two equal parts. Construct a line R through point Y perpendicular to segment segment XJ. Find point T such that line N is the perpendicular bisector of segment from A to T. Determine the point M where segment segment XJ intersects line N. Reflect point X across line R, and call the resulting point D. Compute the angle B formed by the rays from point T to points M and D. Find the measure of angle MTD.", "answer": "3.1416", "hash": "0abc473fc788ea117b9747a9c87ccc58365b7831a8e7af44eabda33b1ff55697", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_568.txt"}
{"question": "Compute V as the difference between measures 1.2 and 4.1. Compute P as the sum of measures 1.8 and 4.8. Compute Z as the ratio of measure P to measure V. Calculate the value of Z.", "answer": "-2.2759", "hash": "ba34e11a66676c76614fb6e53fdc50cea3aa2cfd78478dfaf0ba74b4642f5159", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_823.txt"}
{"question": "Place a point N. Construct point U at distance 3.5 from point N in a random direction. Create a regular 5-sided polygon beginning at points N and U, name the additional vertices ['M', 'K', 'Z'], and denote the polygon as S. Determine the distance J from point Z to point U. Compute the value of J.", "answer": "5.6631", "hash": "6302986c2e6724ed6e8ed1df917f6c5527c64016ea4d9633d60e0e84b9e94b8e", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_799.txt"}
{"question": "Create a point V. Position a point C so that it is exactly V units from point 9. Find the length K between points V and C. Compute the value of K.", "answer": "9.0", "hash": "67584ff3688a8e6c059915774416bb691a40fd0229da695d00af68e16c517f40", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_685.txt"}
{"question": "Mark a point A. Position point H at a distance of 2.7 from point A, in whichever direction you choose. Identify the midpoint I of the segment connecting points A and H. Construct a regular polygon with 8 sides starting from points H and I, call the new vertices ['E', 'Z', 'M', 'Y', 'G', 'F'], and label the resulting polygon as O. Create a circle S containing points H, G, and A on its circumference. Construct point T8 as the image of point A under inversion in circle circle HGA. Calculate the measure of angle D4 with vertex at E and sides passing through T8 and Y. What is the measure of angle T8EY?", "answer": "3.5343", "hash": "58e05373ce64e86dd587e3443003e777de4e669e97b7a83bee848bcb1a054e51", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_814.txt"}
{"question": "Mark a point Y. Mark a point R such that its distance from point 7 is Y. Find point O such that point Y is the midpoint of the segment from R to O. Establish a line segment N from point O to point R. Compute H as the length of segment segment OR raised to the power of 4. Calculate the value of H.", "answer": "38416.0", "hash": "d2908a358eaa99156997df4a47d231843008c0fa5617ff5bf22a5c5a27410911", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_60.txt"}
{"question": "Place a point Z. Place point O so that it is 4.4 units away from point Z in any direction. Construct a regular polygon with 9 sides starting from points Z and O, call the new vertices ['U', 'K', 'S', 'T', 'R', 'V', 'X'], and label the resulting polygon as P. Define vector N starting at point R and ending at point Z. Construct point R2 by shifting point T in the direction and magnitude of vector N. Establish a line segment B6 from point R2 to point R. What is the length of segment R2R?", "answer": "11.2455", "hash": "4edbbd66a9b51aebae16cc994aa2c9178699bcff302950bc223f035f1040b6d5", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_55.txt"}
{"question": "Position a point Q. Mark point B at a distance of 2.4 from point Q in an arbitrary direction. Construct a regular polygon with 4 sides starting from points Q and B, call the new vertices ['L', 'J'], and label the resulting polygon as I. Calculate the power P of the length of segment segment BL to the exponent 4. Measure the distance Y between points B and J. Calculate the ratio T of measure Y to measure P. Compute the value of T.", "answer": "0.1023", "hash": "a4386fc927166664d0884ba43eee21f8c2955c33612ff44be1a777f9031f2611", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_365.txt"}
{"question": "Position a point C. Place point Y so that it is 3.4 units away from point C in any direction. Establish a circle M with center C and radius equal to the distance from C to Y. Mark a point G such that its distance from point 8 is C. Construct the tangent line G from point G to circle M. Identify the point S common to both circle M and line P. Construct a regular polygon with 8 sides starting from points S and C, call the new vertices ['A', 'U', 'Z2', 'I4', 'C6', 'Z5'], and label the resulting polygon as Q. Determine the area P5 of polygon Q. Calculate the value of P5.", "answer": "55.8166", "hash": "23d8651bb06eb5aa10c4f401191a2afcf7d698e831125b30334ef13699f45aa8", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_966.txt"}
{"question": "Construct a point E. Create a point B at a distance of E from point 4. Form a line D that goes through points E and B. Reflect point E across point B, and call the resulting point J. Locate the midpoint A between points J and E. Determine point R by reflecting point A over line D. Reflect point R across point J, and call the resulting point U. Create a regular 10-sided polygon beginning at points E and J, name the additional vertices ['H5', 'N7', 'P1', 'Z4', 'Q8', 'E3', 'F8', 'G6'], and denote the polygon as Z. Mark the point N6 that is equidistant from both endpoints of segment segment F8G6. Create a line segment N2 between points N6 and U. Find the length of segment N6U.", "answer": "21.4656", "hash": "de87ce975d53d65844f435fcce1b3e0032afe2b656f0074f19d34e3b974abe72", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_407.txt"}
{"question": "Mark a point M. Create a point J at a distance of M from point 10. Create a line segment V between points J and M. Calculate the power B of the length of segment segment JM to the exponent 3. Calculate the value of B.", "answer": "1000.0", "hash": "8b92ac742ef75fda7f2b47321972c5a2524c34426440b71e2785840e542c146f", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_603.txt"}
{"question": "Mark a point D. Position a point M so that it is exactly D units from point 5. Construct point G at distance 3.0 from point D in a random direction. Form a line A that goes through points D and M. Determine point Y by reflecting point D over line A. Create point F on line A so that its distance from point D is 3.7. Construct a circle P passing through points Y, M, and G. Mark the points N and O where line A meets circle circle YMG. Draw a line segment E connecting points F and N. What is the length of segment FN?", "answer": "1.3", "hash": "bbbe33b3be397be70b7f5b758c96b0c33911454cb373cf44d6f2085b41244f40", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_519.txt"}
{"question": "Mark a point D. Position a point U so that it is exactly D units from point 5. Draw a line segment A connecting points U and D. Find the length of segment UD.", "answer": "5.0", "hash": "66a590ebfe306a2fd760f568739910b3c9497bbb84e4a0dd7d36c953b5f738ee", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_587.txt"}
{"question": "Mark a point J. Construct point N at distance 3.9 from point J in a random direction. Find point X such that point N is the midpoint of the segment from J to X. Construct a regular polygon with 9 sides starting from points N and J, call the new vertices ['L', 'A', 'T', 'Z', 'U', 'S', 'O'], and label the resulting polygon as H. Determine the angle H7 created by the three points T, J, and X. What is the measure of angle TJX?", "answer": "1.7453", "hash": "0ca58ab85f84a9f852cbf457e55b527ebd181cf1f2bac2a2ae07a8297846000e", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_773.txt"}
{"question": "Create a point C. Mark point P at a distance of 1.3 from point C in an arbitrary direction. Create a line V connecting points C and P. Find point D such that line V is the perpendicular bisector of segment from P to D. Construct point J as the image of point D when reflected over point C. Find the length B2 between points P and J. Calculate the value of B2.", "answer": "2.6", "hash": "7fb8b47795d38d15ab6b13880b2f2dd2106c64b5edbc7bd5be2b5a8b838e85c8", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_217.txt"}
{"question": "Construct a point D. Position point P at a distance of 4.7 from point D, in whichever direction you choose. Create a line O connecting points D and P. Construct a regular polygon with 9 sides starting from points D and P, call the new vertices ['U', 'Y', 'M', 'L', 'V', 'Z', 'S'], and label the resulting polygon as R. Mark point Q7 on line O at a distance of 1.8 from point M. Measure the angle K9 formed by points Q7, L, and U. Find the measure of angle Q7LU.", "answer": "0.0872", "hash": "178d2d46e050c20e4e8926d07d145704c95de4cda834ca532ffaab1a71df282e", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_837.txt"}
{"question": "Mark a point V. Position a point X. Create a regular 5-sided polygon beginning at points X and V, name the additional vertices ['B', 'S', 'C'], and denote the polygon as M. Determine the angle Y created by the three points S, B, and X. Find the measure of angle SBX.", "answer": "1.2566", "hash": "f40d41decfd7de64ef439e2fa4e03e421ccbd6bf8a24cfccca0a09436fb6060b", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_510.txt"}
{"question": "Place a point G. Create a point U at a distance of G from point 7. Create a regular 10-sided polygon beginning at points U and G, name the additional vertices ['H', 'D', 'J', 'O', 'Y', 'M', 'N', 'F'], and denote the polygon as Z. Form segment T6 joining points M and Y. Find the length of segment MY.", "answer": "7.0", "hash": "f7c6666f87561918bb9b024e04fa6da80460d0666bb4e4d5e9ce612c206e1d7d", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_930.txt"}
{"question": "Position a point E. Place a point X. Form a line M that goes through points E and X. Place point G on line M such that it is 2.5 units away from point X. Position point Z at a distance of 4.6 from point G, in whichever direction you choose. Create a circle Y containing points Z, X, and E on its circumference. Find circle O by reflecting circle circle ZXE through point X. Identify the point V common to both circles circle ZXE and O. Determine the angle I created by the three points E, V, and G. Find the measure of angle EVG.", "answer": "3.1416", "hash": "5c12d99a042fbd41bfad8d95cb0b97b63746b9981896535ec2c40fe61bb204fc", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_663.txt"}
{"question": "Place a point Q. Position a point O so that it is exactly Q units from point 5. Create a line P connecting points O and Q. Create point C on line P so that its distance from point O is 4.9. Compute the angle M formed by the rays from point C to points O and Q. Find the measure of angle OCQ.", "answer": "3.1416", "hash": "8b950a76c973bf9780bdeb9f3e340aae54deb79d6efd420e3127fdb91d5f0343", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_133.txt"}
{"question": "Position a point U. Place point Z so that it is 4.9 units away from point U in any direction. Create a regular 9-sided polygon beginning at points U and Z, name the additional vertices ['Q', 'P', 'L', 'I', 'C', 'F', 'O'], and denote the polygon as J. Establish the lines B6, T8 that divide the angles between segments segment QP and segment PL into equal parts. Locate the point H7 at which line T8 crosses segment segment QP. Construct a regular polygon with 6 sides starting from points H7 and Q, call the new vertices ['J6', 'R1', 'G5', 'V8'], and label the resulting polygon as X2. What is the area of polygon X2?", "answer": "62.3798", "hash": "b744ab3c83a39c05a710adf98cafe41efe93b56c00f1d884eb7e764855b98155", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_959.txt"}
{"question": "Mark a point O. Create a point E at a distance of O from point 4. Construct a regular polygon with 4 sides starting from points E and O, call the new vertices ['C', 'M'], and label the resulting polygon as W. Position a point K at any location on segment segment ME. Measure the angle I formed by points O, M, and K. Find the measure of angle OMK.", "answer": "5.4978", "hash": "d50abdc5bd3a4629f596a4afb0e498c3e035d9113c9760578cd476f6f396ff7e", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_375.txt"}
{"question": "Mark a point G. Create a point Q at a distance of G from point 4. Form a circle R centered at point Q such that point G lies on it. Invert point G with respect to circle R, and call the resulting point F. Create a regular 3-sided polygon beginning at points F and Q, name the additional vertices ['T'], and denote the polygon as O. Mark a point Z that lies on segment segment TF. Mark point X9 at a distance of 4.5 from point Z in an arbitrary direction. Measure the distance I3 between points X9 and Z. Compute the value of I3.", "answer": "4.5", "hash": "b2b59c0c23737c80d2dbbabd78713d6e26235f35a8cd9f8efdc83a84b49f6460", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_385.txt"}
{"question": "Position a point N. Construct point Z at distance 1.7 from point N in a random direction. Construct point A as the image of point N when reflected over point Z. Create point L as the reflection of point A across point N. Construct a regular polygon with 9 sides starting from points L and N, call the new vertices ['T', 'V', 'S', 'W', 'Y', 'H', 'X'], and label the resulting polygon as O. Find point C such that point Y is the midpoint of the segment from X to C. Create a regular 5-sided polygon beginning at points S and H, name the additional vertices ['W1', 'M2', 'H8'], and denote the polygon as L4. Construct a circle W2 with center C and radius equal to the length of segment segment M2H8. Compute the value T6 equal to the radius of circle W2. Compute the value of T6.", "answer": "8.6091", "hash": "a73096a02fdf467cae819d192675e5591231b908f907d69e567d11a9e97c042a", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_498.txt"}
{"question": "Create a point C. Place a point F that is C units away from point 2. Construct the perpendicular bisector N of points C and F. Draw a circle V centered at C that passes through point F. Locate the points L and A at which line N crosses circle V. Establish vector X pointing from point A toward point F. Create point Q by translating point A along vector X. Find the length R between points L and Q. Compute the value of R.", "answer": "2.0", "hash": "410d5653b8a1c5bfe7acdd7faeae3cdc5f4cab5321439a42ad68aee956d6c93d", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_58.txt"}
{"question": "Place a point B. Construct a point Z at distance B from point 9. Draw a line segment L connecting points Z and B. Draw a circle E centered at Z with radius equal to the length of segment segment ZB. Construct the tangent line G from point B to circle E. Create a line W through point B that never intersects line G. Mark point X on line W at a distance of 2.1 from point B. Construct circle N as the image of circle E when reflected across line W. Invert point B with respect to circle N, and call the resulting point C. Create a regular 8-sided polygon beginning at points C and X, name the additional vertices ['L1', 'D2', 'F5', 'K7', 'H2', 'U7'], and denote the polygon as Q. Calculate the area V8 of polygon Q. Calculate the value of V8.", "answer": "21.2934", "hash": "403c875898e97e0b0bf6590f6bea25ce78da3794e239b77938759fa124e06592", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_414.txt"}
{"question": "Create a point M. Construct a point N. Reflect point M across point N, and call the resulting point Q. Find the measure of angle X formed by points M, N, and Q. Find the measure of angle MNQ.", "answer": "3.1416", "hash": "df86d4c36d1dc503a1a0e2cfd02d7097c83175762da343ead5f9b8c1b52a0ec4", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_955.txt"}
{"question": "Place a point H. Create point O such that it lies 5.0 units from point H in any direction. Establish a line segment C from point O to point H. Calculate the power F of the length of segment segment OH to the exponent 5. Compute Q as measure F raised to the power of 2. Compute the value of Q.", "answer": "9765625.0", "hash": "daf0f7dffd5f4516724bb2f761c4ab1e85d10bce789c2c2250e46bd029035e28", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_499.txt"}
{"question": "Place a point B. Construct a point F at distance B from point 9. Construct a regular polygon with 9 sides starting from points F and B, call the new vertices ['K', 'G', 'N', 'Q', 'T', 'S', 'Z'], and label the resulting polygon as P. Create the lines X, E that bisect the angles between segments segment SZ and segment BK. Reflect point G across line X, and call the resulting point Y6. Create a regular 4-sided polygon beginning at points Y6 and F, name the additional vertices ['H8', 'Z3'], and denote the polygon as H9. Construct segment A2 from point B to point Z3. Find the length of segment BZ3.", "answer": "28.0521", "hash": "1b0895e92332227dde3347560a0bdeed9697a0f9249ebc7d4c9a5d0c2b2ff003", "original_filename": "passed/1745412668/construction_311.txt"}
